<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Mr. Ånand</title><link>https://astrodevil.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Mr. Ånand</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 11:22:05 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://astrodevil.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Some Useful GitHub Repositories To Enhance Your Web3 Skills</title><link>https://astrodevil.github.io/posts/some-useful-github-repositories-to-enhance-your-web3-skills/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 11:22:05 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://astrodevil.github.io/posts/some-useful-github-repositories-to-enhance-your-web3-skills/</guid><description>GitHub Repositories you can contribute to and enhance your practical knowledge of web3 technologies.</description></item><item><title>GirlScript Summer of Code Learning And Experiences: From Contributor To Project Admin</title><link>https://astrodevil.github.io/posts/girlscript-summer-of-code-learning-and-experiences/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 22:12:05 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://astrodevil.github.io/posts/girlscript-summer-of-code-learning-and-experiences/</guid><description>GSSoC stands for GirlScript Summer of Code. It is a three-month-long Open-Source Program conducted by the GirlScript Foundation for beginners. This year I am selected as project admin for the program. (GSSOC&amp;#39;22)
In this article, I am going to share my experiences from being a contributor in an open-source program to the project admin &amp;amp; mentor of one.</description></item><item><title>Make Your GitHub Profile Standout To Attract Better Opportunities</title><link>https://astrodevil.github.io/posts/make-your-github-profile-standout-to-attract-better-opportunities/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 11:00:05 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://astrodevil.github.io/posts/make-your-github-profile-standout-to-attract-better-opportunities/</guid><description>To screen candidates, the industry is shifting away from resumes and toward GitHub profiles. In the software industry, Open Source projects are widely regarded now. How can recruiters know that the abilities you claim to have are truly the skills you have? When you&amp;#39;re a fresher with no professional experience open-source contributions come in useful. Without any prior industry expertise, GitHub allows you to exhibit your work. As a result, it&amp;#39;s important to make GitHub Profile stand out and present the best version of yourself.</description></item><item><title>15 Recommended Books For Computer Science Students</title><link>https://astrodevil.github.io/posts/15-recommended-books-for-computer-science-students/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 10:56:05 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://astrodevil.github.io/posts/15-recommended-books-for-computer-science-students/</guid><description>We are in the modern world where the digitization of education is already going on. Now lots of blogs, articles are there on the internet to learn from. But Book has its own value, the author puts his all knowledge experience and time to write one whole book. The knowledge and details you get from a book are very precious.</description></item><item><title>40+ No Code/Low Code Tools And Resources For Developers In 2022</title><link>https://astrodevil.github.io/posts/40+-no-codelow-code-tools-and-resources-for-developers-in-2022/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 17:40:05 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://astrodevil.github.io/posts/40+-no-codelow-code-tools-and-resources-for-developers-in-2022/</guid><description>There are so many no-code tools to make the work of developers easier. Anyone can build some useful products, startups without writing even a single line of code. In this article, we will see 40+ No Code/Low Code Tools And Resources For Developers that is going to help you In 2022.
90% of developers don’t know about these resources.</description></item><item><title>All Resources To Help You Start Your Open-Source Journey: Open Source Gallery</title><link>https://astrodevil.github.io/posts/all-resources-to-help-you-start-your-open-source-journey-open-source-gallery/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 17:37:05 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://astrodevil.github.io/posts/all-resources-to-help-you-start-your-open-source-journey-open-source-gallery/</guid><description>Do you want to start your open source journey? Don&amp;#39;t know where to start? Difficulty in finding suitable projects according to your tech stack? Then this article is for you. In this article, I am going to discuss a resource gallery that I curated to help beginners get into the open-source world.
Tutorials, Docs, Projects, and Communities to Get You Started.</description></item><item><title>25 Must-Visit Killer Websites For Developers</title><link>https://astrodevil.github.io/posts/25-must-visit-killer-websites-for-developers/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 17:31:05 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://astrodevil.github.io/posts/25-must-visit-killer-websites-for-developers/</guid><description>There are so many websites to make the work of developers easier. Everyone doesn&amp;#39;t know all. In this article, we will see 25 Must-Visit Killer Websites For Developers.
90% of developers don’t know about these websites</description></item><item><title>How NOT to contribute to Open Source on GitHub: Tips For Beginners</title><link>https://astrodevil.github.io/posts/how-not-to-contribute-to-open-source-on-github-tips-for-beginners/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 17:29:05 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://astrodevil.github.io/posts/how-not-to-contribute-to-open-source-on-github-tips-for-beginners/</guid><description>While maintaining some projects on GitHub during Hacktoberfest 2021, I came across many new open source contributors. They are just starting their open-source journey and making mistakes. In the beginning, making mistakes is not a bad thing. But, correctly contributing to open-source projects is also very important.
In this article, I am going to discuss some tips on - How Not to contribute to Open-Source on GitHub.</description></item><item><title>Are You A Coder? Here Are 20 Top Tips From The Coding Community</title><link>https://astrodevil.github.io/posts/are-you-a-coder-here-are-20-top-tips-from-the-coding-community/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 16:52:05 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://astrodevil.github.io/posts/are-you-a-coder-here-are-20-top-tips-from-the-coding-community/</guid><description>Learning to code is an amazing thing. How you can code something interesting and then view its fascinating outcomes. But Doing it in the right way is also very important. While scrolling YouTube I found a video where some developers and community leaders were sharing their tips about programming.
In this Article, I am going to share 20 Top Tips From The Coding Community</description></item><item><title>Some Cool GitHub Actions You Won't Believe Exists</title><link>https://astrodevil.github.io/posts/some-cool-github-actions-you-wont-believe-exists/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 17:50:05 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://astrodevil.github.io/posts/some-cool-github-actions-you-wont-believe-exists/</guid><description>With GitHub Actions, you can automate, customize, and execute your software development workflows right in your repository. You may find, create, and distribute actions for any job you want to do, including CI/CD, and combine actions in a fully customized workflow.
In this Article, I am going to discuss Some Cool GitHub Actions You Won&amp;#39;t Believe Exists.</description></item><item><title>Some Apps You Should Use As a Student Developer</title><link>https://astrodevil.github.io/posts/some-apps-you-should-use-as-a-student-developer/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 20:57:05 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://astrodevil.github.io/posts/some-apps-you-should-use-as-a-student-developer/</guid><description>Having useful apps in phones is very important now-a-days. And as a student you must use apps useful for you.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://astrodevil.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://astrodevil.github.io/about/</guid><description>About🙏🏼 🎓 I am currently pursuing my Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s in Computer Science Engineering.
🌱 I am currently learning Web Development and writing Tech Articles.
🎯 My Goal is to Contribute to as many Open Source projects as possible.
✨ I love to create different types of Contents.
My Experiences🧑🏼‍💻 GSSoC&amp;rsquo; 22 Project Admin: Collaborating with maintainers and contributors for ZeroOctave-JavaScript-Projects. GSSoC'21 Participant: Contributed to some projects, mainly based on Web Development. DWoC'21 Mentor: Helped contributors to collaborate on projects during 2 months period.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://astrodevil.github.io/featured/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://astrodevil.github.io/featured/</guid><description>Articles For Others🤝🏼 flycode
Say No to Coding! Introduction to Low-Code / No-Code Featured On daily.dev🔥 Some Useful GitHub Repositories To Enhance Your Web3 Skills GirlScript Summer of Code Learning And Experiences: From Contributor To Project Admin Make Your GitHub Profile Standout To Attract Better Opportunities All Resources To Help You Start Your Open-Source Journey: Open Source Gallery 25 Must-Visit Killer Websites For Developers Featured On DevDojo🔥 Some Useful GitHub Repositories To Enhance Your Web3 Skills Some Apps You Should Use As a Student Developer 40+ No Code/Low Code Tools And Resources For Developers In 2022 25 Must-Visit Killer Websites For Developers Featured On GirlScript Summer of Code Blog🔥</description></item><item><title/><link>https://astrodevil.github.io/gallery/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://astrodevil.github.io/gallery/</guid><description>Open Source📚 Wants to start open-source? Are you a beginner? Don&amp;rsquo;t know how, where, why to start?
You are welcome! You are in right place.😊
Open-Source-Gallery provides you with all the resources needed to become a good open-source contributor, project maintainer &amp;amp; developer.
The motive🎯 of this project is to help new learners like you to get familiar with the world of open-source.
Happy learning.👍
Developer Tech🔮 A curated list of Gadgets a developer needs in the different price ranges.</description></item></channel></rss>