<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Websites on Mr. Ånand</title><link>https://mranand.com/categories/websites/</link><description>Recent content in Websites on Mr. Ånand</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 10:56:05 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mranand.com/categories/websites/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>15 Recommended Books For Computer Science Students</title><link>https://mranand.com/blogs/15-recommended-books-for-computer-science-students/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 10:56:05 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://mranand.com/blogs/15-recommended-books-for-computer-science-students/</guid><description>We are in the modern world where the digitization of education is already going on. Now lots of blogs, articles are there on the internet to learn from. But Book has its own value, the author puts his all knowledge experience and time to write one whole book. The knowledge and details you get from a book are very precious.</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We are in the modern world where the digitization of education is already going on. Now lots of blogs, articles are there on the internet to learn from. But Book has its own value, the author puts his all knowledge experience and time to write one whole book. The knowledge and details you get from a book are very precious.</p>
<p>In this article, I am going to discuss 15 Recommended Books For Computer Science Students</p>
<h3 id="1-clean-code-a-handbook-of-agile-software-craftsmanshiphttpsamznto3f96hka">1. <a href="https://amzn.to/3F96hkA">Clean Code: A Handbook of Agile Software Craftsmanship</a></h3>
<p><a href="https://amzn.to/3F96hkA"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1641891220161/uLyxG3zNT.jpeg" alt="cc.jpg"  />
</a></p>
<p>Because it&rsquo;s more approachable, especially for inexperienced developers, Clean Code is one of the most regularly seen books on a programmer&rsquo;s desk. Clean Code focuses on tactical ideas, such as how to build classes and functions, rather than high-level procedures.</p>
<h3 id="2-head-first-javahttpsamznto3fem9ct">2. <a href="https://amzn.to/3Fem9Ct">Head First Java</a></h3>
<p><a href="https://amzn.to/3Fem9Ct"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1642410737622/8H298dREE.jpeg" alt="510l5fQkfoL.jpg"  />
</a></p>
<p>Learning a difficult new language, especially an object-oriented computer programming language like Java, is no simple undertaking. You could believe the issue is with your mind. It appears to have its own mind, one that doesn&rsquo;t always want to take in the dry, technical information you&rsquo;re required to learn. This book is like bible for java beginners.</p>
<h3 id="3-java-the-complete-referencehttpsamznto3gcvnf8">3. <a href="https://amzn.to/3GCVnF8">Java: The Complete Reference</a></h3>
<p><a href="https://amzn.to/3GCVnF8"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1642411110679/WMXzl9Q-J.png" alt="image.png"  />

</a>
In &ldquo;Java: The Complete Reference, Eighth Edition,&rdquo; popular programming author Herb Schildt covers all you need to know about writing, building, debugging, and running Java programmes. This comprehensive volume covers the whole Java language, including syntax, keywords, and core programming concepts, and has been updated for Java Platform, Standard Edition 7 (Java SE 7). You&rsquo;ll also learn about the key components of the Java API library. Swing, JavaBeans, servlets, and applets are all addressed, with real-world examples to demonstrate how they function. Try-with-resources, strings in switch, type inference with the diamond operator, NIO.2, and the Fork/Join Framework are all covered in detail.</p>
<h3 id="4-cracking-the-coding-interviewhttpsamznto3ftnw7l">4. <a href="https://amzn.to/3ftNW7l">Cracking the Coding Interview</a></h3>
<p><a href="https://amzn.to/3ftNW7l"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1642415984437/csfrM0fqU.png" alt="image.png"  />
</a></p>
<p>Cracking the Coding Interview is well worth your time and money if you&rsquo;re ready to start interviewing with FAANG firms. Everything from the interview procedure to unique scenarios, pre-interview preparation to behavior questions, Big O to technical questions, and 189 real-world programming problems are covered.</p>
<h3 id="5-introduction-to-algorithmshttpsamznto3i8mdqm">5. <a href="https://amzn.to/3I8MDqM">Introduction to Algorithms</a></h3>
<p><a href="https://amzn.to/3I8MDqM"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1642411866958/BmiIkLEHg.png" alt="image.png"  />
</a></p>
<p>This book examines a wide range of algorithms in depth while making their creation and analysis accessible to readers of all levels. Each chapter is self-contained and can be utilized as a study unit on its own. The algorithms are given in English and pseudocode that anyone who has done some programming may understand. Without losing the depth of information or mathematical rigor, the explanations have been kept simple.</p>
<h3 id="6-data-structures-and-algorithms-made-easyhttpsamznto3genuks">6. <a href="https://amzn.to/3GEnUKs">Data Structures And Algorithms Made Easy</a></h3>
<p><a href="https://amzn.to/3GEnUKs"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1642415939523/K2h6xcVUK.png" alt="image.png"  />
</a></p>
<p>&ldquo;Data Structures And Algorithms Made Easy: Data Structures and Algorithmic Puzzles&rdquo; addresses questions about complex data structures and algorithms. Because each problem has several solutions and the book is written in C/C++, it may be used as an interview and test preparation tool for computer scientists.
Easy Data Structures and Algorithms: Data Structures and Algorithmic Puzzles is a collection of solutions to a variety of difficult problems involving data structures and algorithms. Any expert in computer science will find it useful. It may be used as a reference manual for computer science professionals. This book will assist you in preparing for campus interviews, exams, and employment. In a word, this book presents solutions to a wide range of challenging data structures.</p>
<h3 id="7-the-algorithm-design-manualhttpsamznto3qzqra1">7. <a href="https://amzn.to/3qzqrA1">The Algorithm Design Manual</a></h3>
<p><a href="https://amzn.to/3qzqrA1"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1642415902363/TzCVeT6QW.png" alt="image.png"  />
</a></p>
<p>The &ldquo;mystery&rdquo; of building algorithms and measuring their usefulness and efficiency is removed in this substantially extended and updated third edition of the best-selling classic. The book currently serves as the fundamental textbook for algorithm design classes, while also serving as the foremost practical reference guide on algorithms for programmers, researchers, and students, with updates to the first and second editions.</p>
<p>The user-friendly format The Algorithm Design Manual makes combinatorial algorithms technology accessible to anybody, with a focus on design rather than analysis. The first section, Techniques, explains how to develop and analyse computer algorithms in a clear and understandable manner. The second section, Resources, has a library of algorithmic resources, implementations, and a wide bibliography for browsing and reference.</p>
<h3 id="8-eloquent-javascripthttpsamznto3a7p6dr">8. <a href="https://amzn.to/3A7p6DR">Eloquent JavaScript</a></h3>
<p><a href="https://amzn.to/3A7p6DR"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1642413043180/IEVC-sVu4.png" alt="image.png"  />
</a></p>
<p>Eloquent JavaScript goes beyond the cut-and-paste scripts found in recipe books to teach you how to write elegant and effective code. Variables, control structures, functions, and data structures are among the first programming concepts you&rsquo;ll study. After that, you&rsquo;ll dive into JavaScript&rsquo;s higher-order functions, closures, and object-oriented programming.</p>
<p>You&rsquo;ll learn how to: Understand the principles of programming and best practises. By combining the capabilities of functional and object-oriented programming, regular expressions may be used to quickly analyse and edit text. Errors and browser incompatibilities should be handled compassionately. Handle browser events and DOM modifications.</p>
<h3 id="9-let-us-chttpsamznto3nzuwsx">9. <a href="https://amzn.to/3nzuWsx">Let Us C</a></h3>
<p><a href="https://amzn.to/3nzuWsx"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1642415822343/HyKx24Kbc.png" alt="image.png"  />
</a></p>
<p>The book&rsquo;s simplicity and storytelling style set it out from the packed shelves of C Programming books. These two characteristics have been present in all six prior versions of this book. Today&rsquo;s C programmer must not only learn the language&rsquo;s complexity and nuances, but also deal with its use in systems such as Windows and Linux. This book does an excellent job of covering all three areas of C programming.</p>
<h3 id="10-head-first-design-patternshttpsamznto3qyzxno">10. <a href="https://amzn.to/3qyzxNo">Head First Design Patterns</a></h3>
<p><a href="https://amzn.to/3qyzxNo"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1642415773733/Q_v0m-FWne.png" alt="image.png"  />
</a></p>
<p>This book teaches you the patterns that matter, when and why to use them, how to apply them to your own ideas, and the object-oriented design concepts that underpin them. Join the hundreds of thousands of developers who have used Head First Design Patterns to enhance their object-oriented design abilities.</p>
<h3 id="11-the-basics-of-bitcoins-and-blockchainshttpsamznto3fexyes">11. <a href="https://amzn.to/3FExyeS">The Basics of Bitcoins and Blockchains</a></h3>
<p><a href="https://amzn.to/3FExyeS"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1642414306694/jfw2Yxacu.png" alt="image.png"  />
</a></p>
<p>Learn about the history and fundamentals of cryptocurrencies and blockchains: There is a wealth of information available about bitcoin and blockchains. However, most of this information may be incomprehensible to the untrained. The Basics of Bitcoins and Blockchains seeks to give an easy-to-understand introduction to this new money and the groundbreaking technology that underlies it.</p>
<h3 id="12-database-system-conceptshttpsamznto3nxbat8">12. <a href="https://amzn.to/3nxBat8">Database System Concepts</a></h3>
<p><a href="https://amzn.to/3nxBat8"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1642414662145/UaK8fkAyS.png" alt="image.png"  />
</a></p>
<p>Database System Concepts is a classic and essential work in database education. It presents the fundamental concepts of database management in an easy-to-understand manner, allowing students to begin working with databases straight away.</p>
<p>The text is aimed towards junior/senior undergraduate database courses or first-year graduate database courses. It also includes additional information that may be utilized as a supplement or as a prelude to a more advanced course.</p>
<h3 id="13-python-crash-coursehttpsamznto3a6wxkt">13. <a href="https://amzn.to/3A6wXkT">Python Crash Course</a></h3>
<p><a href="https://amzn.to/3A6wXkT"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1642415222287/Q7V-MSOlq.png" alt="image.png"  />
</a></p>
<p>Look no further if you need to learn Python as soon as possible. Python Crash Course is designed to get novice Python programmers up and running quickly.
Learn the fundamentals of programming quickly using a project-based approach, so you can focus on what you want to build: websites, data visualization, online apps, or even programming a Raspberry Pi. Python Crash Course is the world&rsquo;s best-selling Python book.</p>
<h3 id="14-designing-data-intensive-applications-the-big-ideas-behind-reliable-scalable-and-maintainable-systemshttpsamznto3rsqezq">14. <a href="https://amzn.to/3rsQeZQ">Designing Data-Intensive Applications: The Big Ideas Behind Reliable, Scalable, and Maintainable Systems</a></h3>
<p><a href="https://amzn.to/3rsQeZQ"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1642415371081/U60Ei_rpmE.png" alt="image.png"  />

</a></p>
<p>&ldquo;Foundations of data systems&rdquo; provides an excellent overview of data systems. This section begins by discussing desired database qualities such as dependability, scalability, and maintainability. Database concepts such as the classic relational model, the document model, and graph-based models are investigated. The implementation of data storage and retrieval in databases is then thoroughly explained.
You will learn about SStables, LSM trees, and B-Trees, as well as how they are employed in databases. Data warehousing and column-oriented databases are thoroughly discussed. The distinctions between OLTP and OLAP are presented in a tabular manner. There is a nice introduction to message brokers, protocolbuf, thrift, and avro.</p>
<h3 id="15-object-oriented-programming-with-chttpsamznto3ge7sjp">15. <a href="https://amzn.to/3GE7SjP">Object-Oriented Programming with C++</a></h3>
<p><a href="https://amzn.to/3GE7SjP"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1642415714814/sxl5Smsoz.png" alt="image.png"  />
</a></p>
<p>The book&rsquo;s goal is to provide a comprehensive enrichment of knowledge in the domain of object-oriented programming using C++ as the implementation language. The author has utilized simple language to convey important principles of object-oriented programming and to aid readers&rsquo; comprehension. The same ideas have been implemented in solved examples written in the C++ programming language. The book retains its original style of straightforward writing and includes plenty of solved examples, programming exercises, and additional practice problems.</p>
<h4 id="if-you--my-content-connect-me-on--twitterhttpsmobiletwittercomastrodevil_-or-supports-me-by-buying-me-a-coffeehttpswwwbuymeacoffeecomastrodevil">If You ❤️ My Content! Connect Me on  <a href="https://mobile.twitter.com/Astrodevil_">Twitter</a> or Supports Me By <a href="https://www.buymeacoffee.com/Astrodevil">Buying Me A Coffee☕</a></h4>
]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>25 Must-Visit Killer Websites For Developers</title><link>https://mranand.com/blogs/25-must-visit-killer-websites-for-developers/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 17:31:05 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://mranand.com/blogs/25-must-visit-killer-websites-for-developers/</guid><description>There are so many websites to make the work of developers easier. Everyone doesn&amp;#39;t know all. In this article, we will see 25 Must-Visit Killer Websites For Developers.
90% of developers don’t know about these websites</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There are so many websites to make the work of developers easier. Everyone doesn&rsquo;t know all. In this article, we will see <strong>25 Must-Visit Killer Websites For Developers</strong>.</p>
<h3 id="1-devdocshttpsdevdocsio">1. <a href="https://devdocs.io/">DevDocs</a></h3>
<p>DevDocs brings together numerous API documentation in a single, searchable interface. You will find docs related to various programming languages, technologies in one place.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1638384967813/utLSXf2-U.png" alt="screely-1638384035935.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="2-raysohttpsrayso">2. <a href="https://ray.so/">ray.so</a></h3>
<p>This website allows you to take beautiful screenshots of codes. It also has a dark mode and some preloaded themes for different programming languages. You can also use its VS Code extension.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1638385311659/82S035d0k.png" alt="screely-1638385296060.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="3-poetsohttpspoetso">3. <a href="https://poet.so/">Poet.so</a></h3>
<p>This site is useful for developers who wish to post photos of their tweets on social media. Website transforms your tweet into a beautiful and editable design.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1638385530712/GsADMkksb.png" alt="screely-1638385516106.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="4-roadmapshhttpsroadmapsh">4. <a href="https://roadmap.sh/">roadmap.sh</a></h3>
<p>This website provides roadmaps, guidelines, and other educational content to assist developers in choosing a path and directing their learning. It is very helpful for a beginner as well as a learner who needs guidance.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1638385854363/V8bW_gzx1.png" alt="screely-1638385839901.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="5-lambdatesthttpswwwlambdatestcom">5. <a href="https://www.lambdatest.com/">LambdaTest</a></h3>
<p>LambdaTest is a cloud-based cross-browser testing platform that lets you test web applications on over 2000 different browsers, operating systems, and devices. LambdaTest allows you to test cross-browser compatibility both manually and automatically.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1638386119439/mDXT7rVtt.png" alt="screely-1638386105526.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="6-dailydevhttpsappdailydev">6. <a href="https://app.daily.dev/">daily.dev</a></h3>
<p>It is a platform where you can find so many good articles to read daily. It shows the best articles from various platforms directly in your feed. Stay updated with quality content from various platforms directly into your browser by using its extension.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1638386504039/glWhXS_nQ.png" alt="screely-1638386457871.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="7-showwcasehttpswwwshowwcasecom">7. <a href="https://www.showwcase.com/">Showwcase</a></h3>
<p>Showwcase is a new social media website specially for people who code connect, build community, and find new opportunities. It is a LinkedIn like platform but only focused on developers. You can join and <a href="https://www.showwcase.com/astrodevil">follow me</a> there.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1638386870736/KMtvp18LF.png" alt="screely-1638386858754.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="8-css-trickshttpscss-trickscom">8. <a href="https://css-tricks.com/">CSS-TRICKS</a></h3>
<p>You can master your web development skills by learning every basics about CSS from this website. If you didn&rsquo;t already know, CSS is what makes pages on the web look beautiful.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1638387360963/CZ40Lwai0.png" alt="screely-1638387302168.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="9-medusahttpswwwmedusajscom">9. <a href="https://www.medusajs.com/">Medusa</a></h3>
<p>An open-source Shopify alternative. Medusa is an open-source headless commerce engine that is fast and customizable. It&rsquo;s Free.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1638387765631/u99VAO5fh.png" alt="screely-1638387753072.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="10-smartmockupshttpssmartmockupscom">10. <a href="https://smartmockups.com/">SMARTMOCKUPS</a></h3>
<p>Why give your time learning how to use Photoshop. Smartmockups allow you to generate gorgeous high-resolution mockups straight in your browser and across numerous devices using a single interface. The quickest web-based mockup tool available, No prior experience or abilities are required, and the library of professional mockups is always growing.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1638388146151/XYY-Hey10.png" alt="screely-1638388121263.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="11-code-beautifyhttpscodebeautifyorg">11. <a href="https://codebeautify.org/">Code Beautify</a></h3>
<p>Make your source code more beautiful and easy to read using code to beautify its AI technology will make your source code more attractive and easy to read.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1638388669184/LkNccoLNs.png" alt="screely-1638388657726.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="12-overapihttpsoverapicom">12. <a href="https://overapi.com/">overAPI</a></h3>
<p>For all developers, OverAPI is one of the most beautiful and useful websites. This website has cheatsheets for the majority of programming languages. Take a look at it right now.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1638388599099/SWli6eqLd.png" alt="screely-1638388584887.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="13-responsivelyhttpsresponsivelyapp">13. <a href="https://responsively.app/">Responsively</a></h3>
<p>This is an open-source website that speeds up the development of web apps by 5 times. All target screens are displayed side by side in a single window. Reduces the time it takes to develop!</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1638388914941/fzDk1EbbW.png" alt="screely-1638388903814.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="14-color-hunthttpscolorhuntco">14. <a href="https://colorhunt.co/">Color Hunt</a></h3>
<p>Colorhunt is a website that allows you to select gorgeous colour palettes. Web designers will find it very beneficial to choose beautiful and appealing colours, as well as to accept colour recommendations from other artists and art projects.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1638389100098/2g69Ma1ju.png" alt="screely-1638389088000.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="15-carbonhttpscarbonnowsh">15. <a href="https://carbon.now.sh/">Carbon</a></h3>
<p>This website will help you to create and share beautiful images of your source codes. It also allows you to make changes to the photographs. You should give it a go right now.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1638389339711/JzN9a1yTi.png" alt="screely-1638389329198.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="16-meta-tagshttpsmetatagsio">16. <a href="https://metatags.io/">Meta Tags</a></h3>
<p>It is a website tag generator that also allows you to update and experiment with your content before seeing how it will appear on Google, Facebook, LinkedIn, and other social media sites.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1638389558917/vBV-rOHip.png" alt="screely-1638389538922.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="17-profile-pic-makerhttpspfpmakercom">17. <a href="https://pfpmaker.com/">Profile Pic Maker</a></h3>
<p>This website creates a professional and beautiful profile for each photo in your Web developer portfolio. As a developer, you will be exposed to social media. You only need to upload any of your images, and it will edit and enhance them. Give it a go right now.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1638389794694/Ywlpmxb0a.png" alt="screely-1638389786334.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="18-small-dev-toolshttpssmalldevtools">18. <a href="https://smalldev.tools/">Small Dev Tools</a></h3>
<p>This website offers a variety of free developer tools, including encoders/decoders, HTML/CSS/Javascript formatters, minifies, fake or test data generators, and more. It also allows you to share codes.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1638390009000/3vdcuU143.png" alt="screely-1638389956512.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="19-resumeiohttpsresumeio">19. <a href="https://resume.io/">resume.io</a></h3>
<p>This website allows you to create a quality resume. It will help you to create a professional resume by providing you with well-tested templates. Give it a Try.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1638390270548/U8e1MzxUy.png" alt="screely-1638390259749.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="20-codepenhttpscodepenio">20. <a href="https://codepen.io/">CODEPEN</a></h3>
<p>CodePen is a web-based development platform that allows users to modify front-end languages such as HTML, CSS, and JavaScript without having to install any software. The nicest aspect is that the findings are visible in real-time, making troubleshooting easier. Developers and designers can also exchange code samples (known as pens) with the rest of the world.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1638390510290/Z11dY_2Vv.png" alt="screely-1638390500404.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="21-storytalehttpsstorytaleio">21. <a href="https://storytale.io/">Storytale</a></h3>
<p>Storytale is a website that had collections of illustrations that Make your project eye-catching with awesome characters. It can be used personally and commercially. This is a helpful website for web designers. Get High-class assets for web and mobile projects.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1638390858191/-tZZB4fvS.png" alt="screely-1638390848756.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="22-readmesohttpsreadmeso">22. <a href="https://readme.so/">readme.so</a></h3>
<p>This website allows you to create project README very easily. Its simple editor helps you to quickly add and customize all the sections you need for your project&rsquo;s README. You can use this to create documentation of your open-source projects quickly.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1638391156722/7CiKyNZNv.png" alt="screely-1638391148567.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="23-peppertypehttpswwwpeppertypeai">23. <a href="https://www.peppertype.ai/">Peppertype</a></h3>
<p>Peppertype is a new tool that helps in automating the content production and ideation process. It analyses your business operations, understands your brand and target audience, and then creates fresh content for you using superior machine learning and artificial intelligence. If you are a developer creating content regularly, then this is for you.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1638391381010/rY_Fyi21N.png" alt="screely-1638391370901.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="24-synthesiahttpswwwsynthesiaio">24. <a href="https://www.synthesia.io/">synthesia</a></h3>
<p>Synthesia helps you to create AI-based videos in over 50+ languages. You don&rsquo;t need a camera, microphone, or real face to create video content. You just need to upload your script and you will get an AI video.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1638391829724/zFvA9ViJg.png" alt="screely-1638391816957.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="25-programmer-humorhttpsprogrammerhumorio">25. <a href="https://programmerhumor.io/">Programmer Humor</a></h3>
<p>Even developers also need entertainment. You can visit this website for various memes and jokes related to programming and developers. Have Fun.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1638392080280/sDiDjjAgL.png" alt="screely-1638392067037.png"  />
</p>
<p><strong>Bonus Website</strong>: I used screenshots taken by <strong><a href="https://www.screely.com/">Screely</a></strong> in this Article.</p>
<h4 id="if-you--my-content-connect-me-on--twitterhttpsmobiletwittercomastrodevil_-or-supports-me-by-buying-me-a-coffeehttpswwwbuymeacoffeecomastrodevil">If You ❤️ My Content! Connect Me on  <a href="https://mobile.twitter.com/Astrodevil_">Twitter</a> or Supports Me By <a href="https://www.buymeacoffee.com/Astrodevil">Buying Me A Coffee☕</a></h4>
]]></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>