<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>github on Mr. Ånand</title><link>https://mranand.com/tags/github/</link><description>Recent content in github on Mr. Ånand</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 11:22:05 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mranand.com/tags/github/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Some Useful GitHub Repositories To Enhance Your Web3 Skills</title><link>https://mranand.com/blogs/some-useful-github-repositories-to-enhance-your-web3-skills/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 11:22:05 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://mranand.com/blogs/some-useful-github-repositories-to-enhance-your-web3-skills/</guid><description>GitHub Repositories you can contribute to and enhance your practical knowledge of web3 technologies.</description></item><item><title>Make Your GitHub Profile Standout To Attract Better Opportunities</title><link>https://mranand.com/blogs/make-your-github-profile-standout-to-attract-better-opportunities/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 11:00:05 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://mranand.com/blogs/make-your-github-profile-standout-to-attract-better-opportunities/</guid><description>To screen candidates, the industry is shifting away from resumes and toward GitHub profiles. In the software industry, Open Source projects are widely regarded now. How can recruiters know that the abilities you claim to have are truly the skills you have? When you&amp;#39;re a fresher with no professional experience open-source contributions come in useful. Without any prior industry expertise, GitHub allows you to exhibit your work. As a result, it&amp;#39;s important to make GitHub Profile stand out and present the best version of yourself.</description></item><item><title>All Resources To Help You Start Your Open-Source Journey: Open Source Gallery</title><link>https://mranand.com/blogs/all-resources-to-help-you-start-your-open-source-journey-open-source-gallery/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 17:37:05 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://mranand.com/blogs/all-resources-to-help-you-start-your-open-source-journey-open-source-gallery/</guid><description>Do you want to start your open source journey? Don&amp;#39;t know where to start? Difficulty in finding suitable projects according to your tech stack? Then this article is for you. In this article, I am going to discuss a resource gallery that I curated to help beginners get into the open-source world.
Tutorials, Docs, Projects, and Communities to Get You Started.</description></item><item><title>How NOT to contribute to Open Source on GitHub: Tips For Beginners</title><link>https://mranand.com/blogs/how-not-to-contribute-to-open-source-on-github-tips-for-beginners/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 17:29:05 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://mranand.com/blogs/how-not-to-contribute-to-open-source-on-github-tips-for-beginners/</guid><description>While maintaining some projects on GitHub during Hacktoberfest 2021, I came across many new open source contributors. They are just starting their open-source journey and making mistakes. In the beginning, making mistakes is not a bad thing. But, correctly contributing to open-source projects is also very important.
In this article, I am going to discuss some tips on - How Not to contribute to Open-Source on GitHub.</description></item><item><title>Some Cool GitHub Actions You Won't Believe Exists</title><link>https://mranand.com/blogs/some-cool-github-actions-you-wont-believe-exists/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 17:50:05 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://mranand.com/blogs/some-cool-github-actions-you-wont-believe-exists/</guid><description>With GitHub Actions, you can automate, customize, and execute your software development workflows right in your repository. You may find, create, and distribute actions for any job you want to do, including CI/CD, and combine actions in a fully customized workflow.
In this Article, I am going to discuss Some Cool GitHub Actions You Won&amp;#39;t Believe Exists.</description></item></channel></rss>