<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Productivity on Mr. Ånand</title><link>https://mranand.com/categories/productivity/</link><description>Recent content in Productivity on Mr. Ånand</description><image><url>https://dynamic-og-image-generator.vercel.app/api/generate?title=Technical+Writer%2C+Developer+Advocate&author=Mr.+%C3%85nand&websiteUrl=mranand.com&avatar=https%3A%2F%2Favatars.githubusercontent.com%2Fu%2F73425223%3Fv%3D4&theme=default</url><link>https://dynamic-og-image-generator.vercel.app/api/generate?title=Technical+Writer%2C+Developer+Advocate&author=Mr.+%C3%85nand&websiteUrl=mranand.com&avatar=https%3A%2F%2Favatars.githubusercontent.com%2Fu%2F73425223%3Fv%3D4&theme=default</link></image><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 10:56:05 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mranand.com/categories/productivity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How Developers, CTOs, and Product Managers Are Building Internal Operational Apps in 2023</title><link>https://mranand.com/blogs/how-developers-ctos-and-product-managers-are-building-internal-operational-apps-in-2023/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 10:56:05 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://mranand.com/blogs/how-developers-ctos-and-product-managers-are-building-internal-operational-apps-in-2023/</guid><description>As a developer, let me break it down for you in casual language. Internal apps are like secret weapons for businesses. They&amp;#39;re custom-made applications built specifically for internal use, helping teams work smarter and faster. These apps tackle everyday challenges like managing projects, tracking inventory, or streamlining processes. They&amp;#39;re like your personal sidekick, making your work life easier and more efficient.</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As a developer, let me break it down for you in casual language. Internal apps are like secret weapons for businesses. They&rsquo;re custom-made applications built specifically for internal use, helping teams work smarter and faster. These apps tackle everyday challenges like managing projects, tracking inventory, or streamlining processes. They&rsquo;re like your personal sidekick, making your work life easier and more efficient. </p>
<p>One prominent use case of internal app development is s creating a unified dashboard for sales teams that consolidates data from multiple sources. Sales teams can benefit from this unified dashboard by having a comprehensive view of their sales pipeline, customer interactions, and performance metrics in one place. They can track leads, monitor opportunities, view customer profiles, and access historical data without the need to switch between different applications or interfaces. </p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/a-s-88P7FDstgaCqhQ-QrdBuGynunQhPla6kdSDX7_Ljjv98uX5-ucMLpFqEylO-wQaKncdjyqFJeUKElR5ATj0lite20O8sbVd8MTXlocQ9hZZfLeDxg1Lw-DxsYqp63fEoPNsce8vtTFAYjJFpog" alt=""  />
</p>
<h2 id="making-the-right-call-on-building-internal-apps">Making the right call on building internal apps</h2>
<p>Deciding when to build internal operational apps requires careful consideration of various factors. Here&rsquo;s a decision matrix that can help guide the decision-making process:</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/V1frOl2OlFzytdfocr5MDoDJvrKQgVVGkeImj23JZZV8Pb9Mdr9xfSALzptoIEyeUirQIfhQBW0fbzHaihjuAGfnrW7ksbdDsGuwrxo203utupaEpRNBBCDe5q14z5PiSz7bgGMqpVWCWvQlEqZ5Rg" alt=""  />
</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p><strong>Customizability:</strong> Off-the-shelf solutions may fall short of meeting unique business requirements. Building an internal app allows for customization, tailored to specific needs.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>Integration Challenges:</strong> Existing systems and tools may require seamless integration. Developing an internal app provides the flexibility to integrate with various APIs and databases.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>Data Security:</strong> Privacy and data protection are paramount. By building internal apps, businesses can implement robust security measures and ensure compliance with industry standards.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>Scalability:</strong> As businesses grow, scalability becomes crucial. Internal apps built in-house allow for scalability, accommodating increasing demands and user bases.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>Cost-Effectiveness:</strong> While building internal apps incurs development costs, it can provide long-term cost savings compared to licensing fees for commercial software.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="internal-operational-app-checklist">Internal operational app checklist</h2>
<p><strong>User-Friendly UI/UX:</strong></p>
<p>Craft a seamless user experience with intuitive design, easy navigation, and visually appealing interfaces to enhance user engagement.</p>
<p><strong>Backend Integration:</strong> </p>
<p>Integrate your internal app with existing systems and databases to ensure smooth data flow and real-time updates.</p>
<p><strong>Frontend UI Components:</strong></p>
<p>Utilize reusable UI components and libraries to accelerate development and maintain consistency throughout the app.</p>
<p><strong>Authorization and Authentication:</strong> </p>
<p>Implement robust security measures by incorporating authorization and authentication protocols to protect sensitive data and ensure access control.</p>
<p><strong>Role-Based Access:</strong> </p>
<p>Define user roles and permissions to ensure appropriate data access based on the user&rsquo;s role within the organization.</p>
<p><strong>SAML and SSO Integration:</strong></p>
<p>Integrate SAML (Security Assertion Markup Language) for secure Single Sign-On (SSO), enabling seamless authentication across different systems.</p>
<p><strong>Integration with Identity Providers:</strong> </p>
<p>Implement integrations with identity providers like Okta to enhance authentication, and user management, and ensure a centralized login experience.</p>
<p><strong>Scalability and Performance:</strong></p>
<p>Design the app with scalability in mind, ensuring it can handle growing user bases and maintain optimal performance even under high loads.</p>
<p><strong>AI Assistance:</strong> </p>
<p>Leverage AI technologies to assist in building internal apps, such as natural language processing for chatbots, machine learning for data analysis, or automated code generation for faster development cycles.</p>
<p><strong>Analytics and Monitoring:</strong></p>
<p>Incorporate analytics tools and monitoring systems to gather valuable insights on app usage, performance, and user behavior, allowing for continuous improvements.</p>
<p><strong>Cross-Device Compatibility:</strong> </p>
<p>Develop the app to be responsive and compatible across various devices and screen sizes, ensuring a consistent experience for users.</p>
<p><strong>Documentation and Support:</strong> </p>
<p>Provide thorough documentation and ongoing support to assist users in understanding app features and resolving any issues they may encounter.</p>
<h2 id="how-to-start-building-internal-apps">How to start building internal apps </h2>
<p><strong>1. Get App Objective Clear</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Clearly define the problem your internal app will solve and the goals it aims to achieve.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Understand the purpose of your app to guide the development process and ensure alignment with your organization&rsquo;s needs.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>2. Decide the Technology</strong></p>
<p>Choose the Right Development Approach: Select the appropriate development approach based on your resources, skills, and timeline. You can choose between building the app in-house using internal development teams, outsourcing the development to external agencies, or using low-code or no-code platforms for faster development.</p>
<p>In recent years, low-code development has emerged as a go-to solution for building internal apps. With low-code platforms like <a href="https://www.dronahq.com/?utm_source=medium&amp;utm_medium=pdsocial&amp;utm_campaign=amitesh" target="_blank" class="highlight-line">DronaHQ</a>, developers can leverage a visual development approach, enabling them to create powerful internal tools on existing data sources with minimal coding. Low code empowers businesses to accelerate development cycles, enhance collaboration between business and IT teams, and streamline the app creation process.</p>
<p><strong>3. Build the App</strong></p>
<p>While traditionally coding apps from scratch was the norm, developers are now leveraging the power of low-code tools. With low code, developers can accelerate development cycles, simplify workflows, and achieve faster time-to-market. It&rsquo;s easy to build apps with drag-and-drop interfaces, pre-built components, and seamless integrations, empowering developers to bring their app ideas to life with speed and efficiency.</p>
<p><strong>4. Test and Refine</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Thoroughly test your internal app to identify and resolve any issues or bugs.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Conduct functional testing, user acceptance testing, and performance testing to ensure high-quality standards.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Gather feedback from users and stakeholders to refine and enhance the app&rsquo;s functionality.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>5. Launch and Monitor</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Deploy your internal app to a production environment.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Monitor its performance and ensure it delivers the intended value to users.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Collect user feedback regularly and iterate on the app to align it with evolving requirements and user needs.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="putting-them-all-together-and-choosing-the-right-tech-for-building-internal-apps">Putting them all together and choosing the right tech for building internal apps</h2>
<p>In a nutshell, building internal apps is a journey that requires careful planning, the right technology, and a focus on user needs. Throughout this blog, we&rsquo;ve explored the ins and outs of internal app development, from understanding the objectives to choosing the best technology. </p>
<p>And in this process, we discovered the game-changing power of low-code development.</p>
<p>One standout solution in the low-code arena is <a href="https://www.dronahq.com/signup/?utm_source=medium&amp;utm_medium=pdsocial&amp;utm_campaign=amitesh" target="_blank" class="highlight-line">DronaHQ</a>. With its intuitive drag-and-drop interface, pre-built components, and seamless integrations, DronaHQ makes building internal apps a breeze. Whether you&rsquo;re a developer, CTO, or product manager, DronaHQ provides the tools you need to create customized, user-friendly apps that drive efficiency and streamline processes within your organization.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/6aqmxtJ9Ntuaaj2O7T9g1BeFBsd3IzuOqeqiPWZ8jHa0vR4U6hSCLEkWyP_uAkNRYrZK1c1akJ6H79QCNtEFRVtJbp8XozhH1i6yyUiDQrMtzcmp3QM888YUW7mjnvVFRv2oGp25j7D2QYh34-7bPw" alt=""  />
</p>
<p>I would recommend <a href="https://www.dronahq.com/signup/?utm_source=medium&amp;utm_medium=pdsocial&amp;utm_campaign=amitesh" target="_blank" class="highlight-line"><strong>DronaHQ</strong></a> for building internal operational tools. With its free trial, businesses can experience its powerful low-code platform firsthand. Starting at just $10, DronaHQ offers affordable <a href="https://www.dronahq.com/pricing/?utm_source=medium&amp;utm_medium=pdsocial&amp;utm_campaign=amitesh" target="_blank" class="highlight-line">pricing plans</a> that cater to organizations of all sizes. It empowers users to streamline operational processes, automate workflows, and integrate data from multiple sources. With its user-friendly interface and robust features, DronaHQ is a cost-effective solution for boosting productivity and efficiency within your organization.</p>
<p><strong>Just before we go, here are a few developer features you get with DronaHQ:</strong></p>
<p><strong>1. Drag &amp; Drop builder</strong></p>
<p>It offers a wide range of over 100 flexible, reusable, and feature-rich UI components right out of the box with a drag-and-drop interface. From tables and menus to charts and detailed views, DronaHQ has thoughtfully curated these components to make building interfaces a breeze. </p>
<p><strong>2. Pre-built templates</strong></p>
<p>DronaHQ hooks you up with a huge selection of pre-made templates for internal apps, saving you heaps of time and effort during development. No need to start from scratch – just pick a template, get an option to customize it, and you&rsquo;re good to go!</p>
<p><strong>3. Backend configuration</strong></p>
<p>It provides extensive support for a diverse range of data sources, giving users the flexibility they need. With their dedicated connectors, you can integrate data from sources like Postgres, MySQL, REST, Oracle, Google Sheets, REST APIs, GraphQLs, and many others. This means you can effortlessly build a custom UI layer that connects and harmonizes disparate data sources.</p>
<p><strong>4. Role-based access control</strong></p>
<p>With features like login authentication, email verification, user roles, and permissions, you will have full control over who can access sensitive information and how they interact with your app.</p>
<p><strong>5. Native UI controls</strong> </p>
<p>From file upload and QR scanner to barcode, geolocation, image compressor, GPS, signature, and beyond, get a comprehensive toolkit to enhance user experiences and unlock endless possibilities for your app&rsquo;s functionality.</p>
<p><strong>6. Custom JavaScript</strong></p>
<p>Whether it&rsquo;s designing custom UI components, configuring frontend logic, importing JS libraries, or transforming API responses, DronaHQ empowers you to leverage the full potential of JavaScript to tailor your app exactly the way you want it.</p>
<p><strong>7. Same app for web and mobile</strong></p>
<p>With DronaHQ, you can develop a single portal that seamlessly caters to both mobile and web platforms. No need for duplicate efforts or managing multiple codebases.</p>
<p><strong>8. White-labeled apps</strong></p>
<p>Customize and brand your apps to reflect your unique identity, providing a consistent and seamless user experience across different platforms.</p>
<p><strong>9. Audit logs</strong> </p>
<p>DronaHQ automatically stores information about all the run-level queries, API calls, etc for audit purposes.</p>
<p><strong>10. Add-ons</strong></p>
<p>DronaHQ has recently introduced a few amazing additions to its platform, now you can add webhook or scheduled-based automation to your process with automation add-ons, and you can generate PDF reports instantly for your app data, and also securely embed apps built on DronaHQ to your own custom portals or websites.</p>
<p><strong>11. Security</strong></p>
<p>DronaHQ is SOC-II and ISO 27001 certified, and all plans include SSL encryption to keep your data safe. </p>
<h2 id="why-i-choose-dronahqhttpswwwdronahqcomsignuputm_sourcemediumutm_mediumpdsocialutm_campaignamitesh">Why I choose <a href="https://www.dronahq.com/signup/?utm_source=medium&amp;utm_medium=pdsocial&amp;utm_campaign=amitesh" target="_blank" class="highlight-line">DronaHQ</a>?</h2>
<p>When it comes to building internal operational tools, DronaHQ offers unique advantages that set it apart from other platforms. With its intuitive drag-and-drop builder, extensive library of pre-built templates, and robust features like backend configuration and role-based access control, <a href="https://www.dronahq.com/signup/?utm_source=medium&amp;utm_medium=pdsocial&amp;utm_campaign=amitesh" target="_blank" class="highlight-line"><strong>DronaHQ</strong></a> empowers organizations to streamline processes and enhance productivity. Additionally, its cost-effective pricing plans and user-friendly interface make it an ideal choice for businesses of all sizes seeking efficient and customizable solutions for their operational needs.</p>
<p><strong>Get started building your first internal app, you can sign up for free</strong> <a href="https://www.dronahq.com/signup/?utm_source=medium&amp;utm_medium=pdsocial&amp;utm_campaign=amitesh" target="_blank" class="highlight-line"><strong>here</strong></a><strong>!</strong></p>
<p>Folks, As a tech influencer, I&rsquo;ve explored several tools for building internal applications. Alongside DronaHQ, I recommend considering <a href="https://www.outsystems.com/?utm_source=medium&amp;utm_medium=pdsocial&amp;utm_campaign=DronaHQ" target="_blank" class="highlight-line">OutSystems</a> for enterprise-grade applications, <a href="https://powerapps.microsoft.com/en-us/?utm_source=medium&amp;utm_medium=pdsocial&amp;utm_campaign=DronaHQ" target="_blank" class="highlight-line">Microsoft Power Apps</a> for seamless integration with the Microsoft ecosystem, <a href="https://www.mendix.com/?utm_source=medium&amp;utm_medium=pdsocial&amp;utm_campaign=DronaHQ" target="_blank" class="highlight-line">Mendix</a> for collaboration and agility, <a href="https://appian.com/?utm_source=medium&amp;utm_medium=pdsocial&amp;utm_campaign=DronaHQ" target="_blank" class="highlight-line">Appian</a> for robust process automation, and Salesforce Lightning for tailored Salesforce integration. Each tool offers unique features and advantages, so choose based on your organization&rsquo;s specific requirements and technology stack.</p>
<p><strong>I hope this article will help you build a powerful internal app for your business.</strong></p>
<h4 id="if-you--my-content-connect-me-on--twitterhttpsmobiletwittercomastrodevil_">If You ❤️ My Content! Connect Me on  <a href="https://mobile.twitter.com/Astrodevil_" target="_blank" class="highlight-line">Twitter</a></h4>



<a class="hugo-shortcodes-bmc-button" href="https://www.buymeacoffee.com/Astrodevil">
    <img src="https://img.buymeacoffee.com/button-api/?button_colour=ffdd00&amp;coffee_colour=ffffff&amp;emoji=&amp;font_colour=000000&amp;font_family=Cookie&amp;outline_colour=000000&amp;slug=Astrodevil&amp;text=Buy&#43;me&#43;a&#43;coffee" alt="Buy me a coffee" />
</a>

]]></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>