<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>tools on Mr. Ånand</title><link>https://mranand.com/tags/tools/</link><description>Recent content in tools on Mr. Ånand</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 10:56:05 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mranand.com/tags/tools/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Top 20 Must Try AI Tools for Developers in 2023</title><link>https://mranand.com/blogs/top-20-must-try-ai-tools-for-developers-in-2023/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 10:56:05 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://mranand.com/blogs/top-20-must-try-ai-tools-for-developers-in-2023/</guid><description>In this article, We&amp;#39;ll talk about the top 20 AI and low-code tools designed to empower developers. AI tools are so much more powerful now that it enables them to create impactful products, manage teams and run their own startups. Discover the cutting-edge capabilities of these AI tools and how they can significantly enhance efficiency and innovation in the development process.</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this article, we&rsquo;ll see a few AI-powered tools that are set to revolutionize development and make the life of developers easy in 2023. We&rsquo;ll talk about the top 20 AI and low-code tools designed to empower developers. AI tools are so much more powerful now that it enables them to create impactful products, manage teams and run their own startups. Discover the cutting-edge capabilities of these AI tools and how they can significantly enhance efficiency and innovation in the development process.</p>
<h2 id="1-tldvhttpstldvcellosoaxf1wsxl27m">1. <a href="https://tldv.cello.so/AXf1WSXl27m">tl;dv</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://tldv.cello.so/AXf1WSXl27m"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1689492544546/f0dfc23d-b39a-44e4-b6c1-515488602cea.png" alt="tl;dv"  />
</a></p>
<p>Introducing <strong>tl;dv</strong>, an AI-powered tool for call and meeting management. With AI timestamps, you can effortlessly highlight key moments and automatically generate summaries. Get instant access to recordings, timestamps, and transcripts right after your calls. Quickly find important moments, create clips, and utilize AI search for comprehensive insights across your meeting library.</p>
<p>Whether it&rsquo;s UX research, product management, or customer success, This tool empowers you to enhance productivity, drive user-centric change, and streamline collaboration. Experience the transformative power of AI in optimizing your call workflows today.</p>
<h2 id="2-pieces-for-developershttpspiecesapp">2. <a href="https://pieces.app/">Pieces for Developers</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://pieces.app/"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1689632069086/84a29d20-d1df-4af4-bc1e-5075382bb334.png" alt="Pieces"  />
</a></p>
<p>Pieces for Developers is an intelligent code snippet manager deeply integrated with AI to help you save, generate, enrich, reuse and share code throughout your workflow. The desktop application and suite of integrations with existing developer tools boost your productivity while researching in the browser, collaborating with teammates, and coding in the IDE.</p>
<p>You can generate contextualized code based on your personal repository, extract code from screenshots, automatically add inline comments to your code, and much more - all within a powerful, centralized application that streamlines your workflow. Code more efficiently with their free tools!</p>
<h2 id="3-youhttpsyoucom">3. <a href="https://you.com/">YOU</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://you.com/"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1689493808498/b8a82560-f03d-4266-8720-f5d0ccfca39f.png" alt="YOU"  />
</a></p>
<p>You.com is a search engine built on artificial intelligence that provides users with a customized search experience while keeping their data 100% private. It&rsquo;s a proper app suite with lots of AI-based tools and features. With <strong>YOUwrite</strong>, you can use AI to write blogs, emails or social media posts. With <strong>YOUimagine,</strong> find and create stunning images using AI.</p>
<p>You can write code and take help in your development process by accessing code mode AI chat to search the web. And study or learn new skills by using study mode chat to access resources across the web. Explore YOU now.</p>
<h2 id="4-jamhttpsjamdev">4. <a href="https://jam.dev/">Jam</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://jam.dev/jamgpt"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1689580788138/6f5f6e55-73ca-41d4-b868-4209469ecaa8.png" alt="Jam"  />
</a></p>
<p>Jam.dev is a user-friendly tool trusted by thousands of teams. It enables quick bug reporting without disrupting workflow, generating comprehensive bug reports that include essential information like browser/OS details, console logs, user actions, network logs, and linked services. It seamlessly integrates with popular issue trackers and tools, enhancing bug reporting in any preferred platform.</p>
<p>Additionally, JamGPT, an AI debugging assistant included with Jam, analyzes bug reports, identifies correlations, and provides solutions, allowing for faster debugging powered by AI. JamGPT is available as a free extension for Jam users and as an instant ChatGPT app exclusively for macOS, accessible via a convenient keyboard shortcut.</p>
<h2 id="5-decktopus-aihttpswwwdecktopuscomviamr">5. <a href="https://www.decktopus.com/?via=mr">Decktopus AI</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://www.decktopus.com/?via=mr"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1689667688946/f8bbb738-5665-48f9-a2a3-3e8a04ea8097.png" alt="Decktopus"  />
</a></p>
<p>Decktopus is an invaluable tool for developers and product managers, enabling them to create impressive presentations effortlessly and without design expertise. By saving time and effort, it allows them to concentrate on essential tasks. For developers, Decktopus generates visually appealing presentations for project updates, technical documentation, and product demos, effectively conveying information to diverse audiences.</p>
<p>Product managers can utilize its features to craft engaging presentations for product roadmaps, market research, and customer feedback, utilizing customizable themes, layouts, and design options. Decktopus offers built-in tools such as forms, voice recording, custom domain integration, webhook functionality, and multimedia embedding, enhancing the overall presentation experience.</p>
<h2 id="6-durablehttpsdurableco">6. <a href="https://durable.co/">Durable</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://durable.co/"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1689876016105/a69c77ac-d9cf-46fa-8634-1b9a2a7fa377.png" alt=""  />
</a></p>
<p>Durable can help you build a website in 30 seconds with AI. This AI website builder generates an entire website with images and copies in seconds. If you are a small business owner without coding knowledge, this is a go-to tool for you. You can edit the website with a simple editor or generate a new website design just by writing AI prompts. You can get a website, CRM, analytics and add invoicing without any hectic process.</p>
<p>If you are a developer, you can launch a project page in seconds using Durable. Code less build more!</p>
<h2 id="7-leap-aihttpstryleapairefastro">7. <a href="https://tryleap.ai/?ref=astro">Leap AI</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://tryleap.ai/?ref=astro"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1689494296260/39dc28bd-2325-4e2e-8f2a-c9088f46be15.png" alt="Leap AI"  />
</a></p>
<p>Leap AI provides AI APIs for developers. Covers a wide range of AI tasks, including image recognition, text analysis, and natural language processing. Leap AI&rsquo;s APIs offer user-friendly features, making them accessible even for developers without AI experience. These APIs are scalable, allowing you to adjust the number of requests as per your needs. With reliable performance, you can trust that Leap AI&rsquo;s APIs will be available when required.</p>
<p>If you seek a provider with diverse services, easy-to-use APIs, and scalability, Leap AI is an excellent choice. Integrate with over 5,000+ apps without writing any code.</p>
<h2 id="8-notion-aihttpswwwnotionsoproductai">8. <a href="https://www.notion.so/product/ai">Notion AI</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://www.notion.so/product/ai"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1689497217522/91ff9f27-fb1a-48e0-a949-23ff97116449.png" alt="Notion"  />
</a></p>
<p>Notion AI is a helpful tool inside the Notion workspace, assisting with writing, brainstorming, editing, and summarizing. It boosts writing efficiency and speed, suitable for various content types like blogs, job descriptions, and emails. The &lsquo;Notion AI automates content creation, including blogs, brainstorming, to-do lists, and literature, using powerful artificial intelligence. Unlike other tools, Notion&rsquo;s drag-and-drop text editor allows easy rearrangement and transformation of AI-generated content.</p>
<h2 id="9-microsoft-designerhttpsdesignermicrosoftcom">9. <a href="https://designer.microsoft.com/">Microsoft Designer</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://designer.microsoft.com/"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1689497731903/5b68ec42-776c-4f51-ab56-bacda597d575.png" alt="MS"  />
</a></p>
<p>Microsoft Designer is a versatile tool for crafting signs, invitations, logos, social media posts, and website banners. With its AI capabilities, you can effortlessly begin designing using your own images or AI-generated options. It supports you throughout the creative journey, from ideation to actualization. Equipped with AI superpowers, it can generate striking designs and images based on your input, while providing writing assistance and automatic layout suggestions.</p>
<p>It can help you in the promotion of your software and apps by using visual design generated using AI.</p>
<h2 id="10-microsoft-clipchamphttpsclipchampcomen">10. <a href="https://clipchamp.com/en/">Microsoft Clipchamp</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://clipchamp.com/en/"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1689499024984/983ef9ca-0890-40b8-95c5-213a4b6b246a.png" alt="MS"  />
</a></p>
<p>Clipchamp is an online video editor that enables everyone to craft captivating stories through video. Clipchamp is the go-to platform for effortlessly editing videos for various purposes. Whether starting from scratch or using a template for efficiency, its extensive collection caters to all project types. Importing videos from multiple sources, including computers and mobile phones, is a breeze.</p>
<p>Microsoft is using AI like crazy, this video editor is super easy to use to edit presentations, video tutorials or project introductions. Automatically create accurate captions in over 140 languages. Turn text into speech with one click.</p>
<h2 id="11-superagihttpssuperagicom">11. <a href="https://superagi.com/">SuperAGI</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://superagi.com/"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1689533754815/091e8836-798a-4608-a49b-45c6ddc964cd.png" alt="SuperAGI"  />
</a></p>
<p>SuperAGI is a user-friendly open-source platform for building and launching autonomous agents for different purposes. With its graphical interface, action console, concurrent agents, and various database options, developers can easily create and manage AI agents. SuperAGI is a developer-focused framework for autonomous AI agents, designed to simplify the development process.</p>
<p>It recently introduced SuperCoder, a SuperAGI agent template to create simple software applications using goals &amp; instructions.</p>
<h2 id="12-replicatehttpsreplicatecom">12. <a href="https://replicate.com/">replicate</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://replicate.com/"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1689583036583/666a137e-da14-4dcf-b382-b9262cf4ac3b.png" alt="replicate"  />
</a></p>
<p>Replicate is a cloud-based platform that simplifies machine learning for developers. It offers a scalable API to run open-source models without requiring extensive knowledge of machine learning. Developers can access Replicate&rsquo;s Python library or directly query the API using their preferred tools. The platform hosts a diverse community of machine learning experts who share various models, from language processing to video creation.</p>
<p>With Replicate and tools like Next.js and Vercel, developers can swiftly bring their ideas to life and gain visibility on platforms like Hacker News. Replicate also streamlines model deployment with Cog, an open-source tool that packages models into production-ready containers. Overall, Replicate enables easy and efficient integration of machine learning into projects.</p>
<h2 id="13-hugging-facehttpshuggingfaceco">13. <a href="https://huggingface.co/">Hugging Face</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://huggingface.co/"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1689583354484/1ca9b760-f1b0-4a2c-9e57-a0e3471f24f1.png" alt="Hugging face"  />
</a></p>
<p>Hugging Face is an AI community shaping the future, enabling you to build, train, and deploy cutting-edge models using open-source machine learning. With over 5,000 organizations involved, Hugging Face provides a collaborative hub where creators tackle challenges in Audio, Vision, and Language with AI. Their natural language processing library, Transformers, is open-source and now supports various ML models like Flair, Asteroid, ESPnet, and Pyannote, with more on the way.</p>
<p>Additionally, Hugging Face offers an Inference API for seamless model deployment and the development of innovative technologies, including T0 Multitask Prompted Training, DistilBERT, HMTL, and Dynamical Language Models for enhanced language modeling.</p>
<h2 id="14-pineconehttpswwwpineconeio">14. <a href="https://www.pinecone.io/">Pinecone</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://www.pinecone.io/"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1689583592272/6084bde6-75f8-4e46-8340-540bf9bfd943.png" alt="Pinecone"  />
</a></p>
<p>Pinecone simplifies the development of high-performance vector search apps, offering scalability and ease of use. It empowers AI application builders with reduced overhead and ultra-low latencies, enabling a seamless transition from research to production without DevOps. With Pinecone, you can effortlessly launch, utilize, and scale your AI solution without the need for infrastructure maintenance or algorithm troubleshooting.</p>
<h2 id="15-midjourneyhttpswwwmidjourneycomhome">15. <a href="https://www.midjourney.com/home/">Midjourney</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://www.midjourney.com/home/"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1689588456524/c1614b7b-046d-45df-b944-7bcfcf4a48d7.png" alt="Midjourney"  />
</a></p>
<p>Midjourney is an AI-powered program that generates stunning images using advanced algorithms and state-of-the-art technology. It serves as a valuable tool for developers, enabling them to create visually appealing images for various projects, such as websites, apps, and games. Moreover, developers can leverage Midjourney to explore AI and machine learning techniques, integrating them into their own projects. By incorporating Midjourney, developers can enhance the visual appeal of their work and experiment with cutting-edge AI techniques, making it a powerful tool for their creative endeavours.</p>
<h2 id="16-assemblyaihttpswwwassemblyaicom">16. <a href="https://www.assemblyai.com/">AssemblyAI</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://www.assemblyai.com/"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1689588866426/5023d938-d984-49b1-8980-4f690cabf57c.png" alt="AssemblyAI"  />
</a></p>
<p>AssemblyAI is a leading platform that offers AI models for speech transcription and comprehension. Their user-friendly API provides access to advanced AI models that can recognize speakers, summarize speeches, and more. Leveraging cutting-edge AI research, AssemblyAI delivers reliable and scalable models through a secure API, trusted by numerous startups and enterprises worldwide. With comprehensive resources, including tutorials and documentation, developers can easily integrate AssemblyAI&rsquo;s API to create innovative products incorporating speech recognition and understanding. By utilizing AssemblyAI&rsquo;s state-of-the-art AI models, developers gain a powerful tool for accurately transcribing and comprehending speech data in their projects.</p>
<h2 id="17-chatpdfhttpswwwchatpdfcom">17. <a href="https://www.chatpdf.com/">ChatPDF</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://www.chatpdf.com/"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1689590014693/c7fdda50-7c9f-45f7-9b4c-1d2bb88decb6.png" alt="ChatPDF"  />
</a></p>
<p>ChatPDF is an AI platform that extracts information from PDFs, enabling users to chat with PDF files as if they were talking to a human. It is similar to ChatGPT, but specifically designed for research papers. To use ChatPDF, visit their website and upload a pdf. It offers a chat interface exclusively for interacting with PDFs in real time. This tool allows users to efficiently complete tasks and extract information from large PDF files. It accepts PDFs in any language and can chat in any language.</p>
<h2 id="18-agentgpthttpsagentgptreworkdai">18. <a href="https://agentgpt.reworkd.ai/">AgentGPT</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://agentgpt.reworkd.ai/"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1689591123085/4df55277-7362-4e3c-8663-9dbc87f6228c.png" alt="AgentGPT"  />
</a></p>
<p>AgentGPT is a platform that enables users to create and deploy their own autonomous AI agents online. Users can give their agents a name and objective, and the agents will work towards achieving the assigned goal. Through a chain of language models, the agents think, execute tasks, evaluate their performance, and generate new tasks, recursively advancing towards their objective. With AgentGPT, developers have a powerful tool for creating personalized AI agents capable of accomplishing diverse goals.</p>
<h2 id="19-langchainhttpslangchain-langchainvercelappdocsget_startedintroductionhtml">19. <a href="https://langchain-langchain.vercel.app/docs/get_started/introduction.html">LangChain</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://langchain-langchain.vercel.app/docs/get_started/introduction.html"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1689591738668/77b030c1-8d63-4d87-9dd5-1c3a28d4ccc0.png" alt="LangChain"  />
</a></p>
<p>LangChain is a framework that simplifies application development using large language models. It offers modular abstractions and implementations for various components, making it easy to work with language models. Additionally, LangChain provides customizable use-case-specific chains, enabling developers to quickly start and customize applications for specific purposes like document analysis, chatbots, and code analysis. Overall, LangChain empowers developers to leverage language models effectively and build innovative applications.</p>
<h2 id="20-gretelaihttpsgretelai">20. <a href="https://gretel.ai">Gretel.ai</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://gretel.ai"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1689592373298/9306e54d-cc0e-406f-a3b5-8a1877c1568c.png" alt="Gretel"  />
</a></p>
<p>Gretel ai is a synthetic data platform that enables developers to create artificial datasets resembling real data, ensuring privacy is maintained. With Gretel.ai&rsquo;s APIs, developers can easily generate anonymized and secure synthetic data, accelerating innovation while protecting sensitive information. The platform offers comprehensive tools for training AI models, validating use cases, and generating data as required, with a quick setup time. Developers can explore synthetic data through sample notebooks or the user-friendly web app, catering to both technical and non-technical users. Gretel ai empowers developers to harness the potential of synthetic data while upholding privacy standards.</p>
<h2 id="21-codewphttpscodewpai">21. <a href="https://codewp.ai/">CodeWP</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://codewp.ai/"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1689835584488/e1763aef-d00a-49d9-8b98-55134c81e37d.png" alt="CodeWP"  />
</a></p>
<p>CodeWP is a cutting-edge AI code generator and assistant built for WordPress. With its powerful features and user-friendly interface, it simplifies code creation, testing, and installation. It offers a vast library of verified snippets and tutorials to enhance your skills, making it a valuable tool for all aspects of WordPress development. Just ask the generator, and it will provide custom solutions tailored to your needs.</p>
<p><strong>I hope these AI-based tools and websites will help you as a developer to grow more.</strong></p>
<h4 id="if-you--my-content-connect-me-on--twitterhttpsmobiletwittercomastrodevil_">If You ❤️ My Content! Connect Me on  <a href="https://mobile.twitter.com/Astrodevil_">Twitter</a></h4>



<a class="hugo-shortcodes-bmc-button" href="https://www.buymeacoffee.com/Astrodevil">
    <img src="https://img.buymeacoffee.com/button-api/?button_colour=ffdd00&amp;coffee_colour=ffffff&amp;emoji=&amp;font_colour=000000&amp;font_family=Cookie&amp;outline_colour=000000&amp;slug=Astrodevil&amp;text=Buy&#43;me&#43;a&#43;coffee" alt="Buy me a coffee" />
</a>

]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>40+ No Code/Low Code Tools And Resources For Developers In 2022</title><link>https://mranand.com/blogs/40+-no-codelow-code-tools-and-resources-for-developers-in-2022/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 17:40:05 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://mranand.com/blogs/40+-no-codelow-code-tools-and-resources-for-developers-in-2022/</guid><description>There are so many no-code tools to make the work of developers easier. Anyone can build some useful products, startups without writing even a single line of code. In this article, we will see 40+ No Code/Low Code Tools And Resources For Developers that is going to help you In 2022.
90% of developers don’t know about these resources.</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There are so many no-code tools to make the work of developers easier. Anyone can build some useful products, startups without writing even a single line of code. In this article, we will see <strong>40+ No Code/Low Code Tools And Resources For Developers</strong> that is going to help you In 2022.</p>
<h3 id="what-exactly-is-no-code">What exactly is no-code?</h3>
<p>Programming without code is a concise definition. It is the use of no-code tools that allow you to create a fully functional, responsive web application or website without writing any code. However, it goes a little deeper than that.</p>
<p>Every piece of technology, including no-code platforms, is developed with code. The distinction is that no-code platforms provide building elements that are required by any website or application, such as pages, data storage and display, individual user profiles, and file upload. People may then link them into their own program using drag and drop or other &ldquo;human-understood&rdquo; actions that do not require coding.</p>
<h3 id="1-zapierhttpszapiercom">1. <a href="https://zapier.com/">Zapier</a></h3>
<p>For folks who are always on the go, automation is a great way to save time. Zapier automates the transfer of data across your online apps, allowing you to focus on your most critical tasks.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1639572301955/UV_W_wM64.png" alt="screely-1639572286580.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="2-font-flipperhttpsfontflippercom">2. <a href="https://fontflipper.com/">FONT FLIPPER</a></h3>
<p>You can preview 500+ google fonts on top of your designs using this website.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1639572754874/u1_Pb7TYB.png" alt="screely-1639572746616.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="3-figmahttpswwwfigmacom">3. <a href="https://www.figma.com/">Figma</a></h3>
<p>Figma integrates everyone involved in the design process, allowing teams to produce better products in less time. You can create beautiful designs for your work. The “always online” nature of Figma actually provides some of the greatest strengths of the tool. One of those strengths is that Figma allows for live, real-time collaboration. Free + Paid</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1639573000906/9Oz4jawWt.png" alt="screely-1639572987345.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="4-previewedhttpspreviewedapp">4. <a href="https://previewed.app/">Previewed</a></h3>
<p>Previewed helps to create smart mockups by just dragging and dropping in the browser. You can create device shots and animated clips.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1639573395005/RSQHQEas6.png" alt="screely-1639573384652.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="5-nocodeapihttpsnocodeapicom">5. <a href="https://nocodeapi.com/">NoCodeAPI</a></h3>
<p>NoCodeAPI helps you to set up your Google Sheets, Airtable, Google Analytics, Twitter, Telegram, Open Graph API, MailChimp, and 50+ other apps without a backend to save time and money.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1639573722110/AQsGr38Wa.png" alt="screely-1639573709300.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="6-splinehttpssplinedesign">6. <a href="https://spline.design/">Spline</a></h3>
<p>Spline helps you to create beautiful 3D designs to use for your projects and websites.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1639573928254/5hYR78k-w.png" alt="screely-1639573917553.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="7-removebghttpswwwremovebg">7. <a href="https://www.remove.bg/">removebg</a></h3>
<p>You can remove the background of any image without a click. There are a lot of beautiful backgrounds to choose from.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1639574493676/yX3NhOfWj.png" alt="screely-1639574482800.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="8-coolorshttpscoolorsco">8. <a href="https://coolors.co/">Coolors</a></h3>
<p>The lightning-quick colour scheme generator! Create your ideal colour scheme or get inspired by thousands of stunning colour schemes.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1639576693553/Mv2tCxiSk.png" alt="screely-1639576682616.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="9-webflowhttpswebflowcom">9. <a href="https://webflow.com/">Webflow</a></h3>
<p>Webflow lets you create your own website without writing any code. More than 3,500,000 designers and teams use Webflow to build, collaborate on, and develop amazing websites on a totally visual canvas – no code required. It is a visual interface builder for digital interfaces. It essentially enables you to position and design parts of any digital interface.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1639576948150/S22Y_9utg.png" alt="screely-1639576940938.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="10-seo-site-checkuphttpsseositecheckupcom">10. <a href="https://seositecheckup.com/">SEO Site Checkup</a></h3>
<p>SEO Site Checkup performs a quick audit of your website, checking for proper tags and highlighting any errors that may arise. Analyze your SEO concerns in real-time. You can analyze and act on SEO reports.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1639577212769/cPDFXW-oh.png" alt="screely-1639577204965.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="11-typeformhttpswwwtypeformcom">11. <a href="https://www.typeform.com/">Typeform</a></h3>
<p>Make forms, surveys, and quizzes that people want to fill out. You can create integrations with various apps to enjoy your time-saving workflow. Free + Paid</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1639577626023/FrnH6DRit.png" alt="screely-1639577615142.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="12-mockuuups-studiohttpsmockuuupsstudio">12. <a href="https://mockuuups.studio/">Mockuuups Studio</a></h3>
<p>Your search for the ideal mockups has come to an end. Designers and marketers can drag and drop graphics into 1200+ mockups in seconds.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1639578884276/eT3FF7UbtY.png" alt="screely-1639578871929.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="13-extensiondevhttpsextensiondev">13. <a href="https://extension.dev/">extension.dev</a></h3>
<p>extension.dev is a low-code platform for building and deploying browser extensions that help you grow your business. Use their library of sample extensions and templates to get started right away, or start from scratch. Free</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1639579795286/v2pYc4QsQ.png" alt="screely-1639579787004.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="14-flaticonhttpswwwflaticoncom">14. <a href="https://www.flaticon.com/">flaticon</a></h3>
<p>Download free icons and stickers for your projects. Resources made by and for designers. PNG, SVG, EPS, PSD and BASE 64 formats. Access 6M+ vector icons &amp; stickers.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1639579961292/G-6sXFUYR.png" alt="screely-1639579954187.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="15-freepikhttpswwwfreepikcom">15. <a href="https://www.freepik.com/">freepik</a></h3>
<p>Find tons of graphic resources including Free Vectors, Stock Photos and PSD.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1639580197830/_tGft6H5V.png" alt="screely-1639580189268.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="16-landinpagefyihttpslandingpagefyiindexhtml">16. <a href="https://landingpage.fyi/index.html">landin&rsquo;page.fyi</a></h3>
<p>Build your best landing page with hand-picked examples and tools. A curated library of landing page resources. You&rsquo;ll have a up-to-date landing pages in no time.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1639584539538/Zv6JP7TtG.png" alt="screely-1639581335519.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="17-framerhttpswwwframercomfp">17. <a href="https://www.framer.com/fp/">Framer</a></h3>
<p>Create stunning interactive designs from start to finish all on the canvas. Design realistic websites and apps in minutes with pre-made interactive components, polished assets, layout tools, and more.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1639585505868/Zl4_-fmfn.png" alt="screely-1639585442568.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="18-tailshttpsdevdojocomtails">18. <a href="https://devdojo.com/tails">Tails</a></h3>
<p>Tails is the ultimate drag&rsquo;n drop page creator built for TailwindCSS. Over 220+ components to help you look pretty for your customers. Free + Paid</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1639585656041/Mh3CQqHkA.png" alt="screely-1639585647430.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="19-panelbearhttpspanelbearcom">19. <a href="https://panelbear.com/">Panelbear</a></h3>
<p>Panelbear helps you to measure your website&rsquo;s most important metrics, so you can deliver a great end user experience.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1639585783544/aSZnmRQ6G.png" alt="screely-1639585774444.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="20-copyaihttpswwwcopyai">20. <a href="https://www.copy.ai/">copy.ai</a></h3>
<p>With CopyAI’s automated creativity tools,
you can generate marketing copy in seconds.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1639585969921/4HDhG0jwv.png" alt="screely-1639585961526.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="21-poryhttpsporyio">21. <a href="https://pory.io/">PORY</a></h3>
<p>Create your app the way you like using drag and drop blocks. Connect your data from all your favourite apps. Control what users can view, create and modify with user groups.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1639594064531/6Plx5DM89.png" alt="screely-1639594056888.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="22-shoutouthttpsshoutoutso">22. <a href="https://shoutout.so/">Shoutout</a></h3>
<p>Increase your consumer base by emphasising why people trust you. Shoutout makes it simple to take your current social proof and transform it into a lovely &ldquo;Wall of Love.&rdquo; In less than 3 minutes, you can capture, curate, and publish a wall.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1639594283814/pUreMBUec.png" alt="screely-1639594272618.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="23-codahttpscodaiowelcome">23. <a href="https://coda.io/welcome">Coda</a></h3>
<p>Coda comes with building blocks—like tables and buttons—and time-saving templates, so your doc can grow and evolve with the needs of your team. No more ping-ponging between documents, spreadsheets, and niche workflow apps to get things done. Coda brings all of your words and data into one flexible surface.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1639594582745/Cov2R2wnQ.png" alt="screely-1639594574771.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="24-buildfirehttpsbuildfirecom">24. <a href="https://buildfire.com/">BuildFire</a></h3>
<p>The Most Powerful App Maker For iOS &amp; Android. BuildFire’s powerful and easy to use mobile app builder makes it so you can create mobile apps for iOS &amp; Android in a fraction of the time and cost.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1639594710073/c0WH_eNvF.png" alt="screely-1639594695102.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="25-bubblehttpsbubbleio">25. <a href="https://bubble.io/">bubble</a></h3>
<p>The best way to build web apps without code. Bubble is the most powerful no-code platform, empowering entrepreneurs to build production-ready web apps.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1639594815486/Vii3I5Yz3.png" alt="screely-1639594807266.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="26-pagelyhttpswwwpagelysite">26. <a href="https://www.pagely.site/">PAGELY</a></h3>
<p>Build beautiful websites In light speed. No coding required.
Launch websites from Notion, Google Sheets, GitHub or Airtable.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1639595012287/yyY-q98bu.png" alt="screely-1639595001653.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="27-buildboxhttpssignupbuildboxcom">27. <a href="https://signup.buildbox.com/">BUILDBOX</a></h3>
<p>Create 2D and 3D game without any coding. Try this awesome low code game development platform. Build any game from scratch or use templates.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1639595280014/XJ8uzBGNu.png" alt="screely-1639595266472.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="28-wicked-templateshttpswwwwickedtemplatescom">28. <a href="https://www.wickedtemplates.com/">Wicked Templates</a></h3>
<p>Find HTML landing page templates here. You can get Free and Premium themes, UI Kit&rsquo;s, templates and landing pages built with Tailwind CSS, HTML &amp; Next.js.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1639595598609/AVvVKHPX_.png" alt="screely-1639595590089.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="29-airtablehttpswwwairtablecom">29. <a href="https://www.airtable.com/">Airtable</a></h3>
<p>Airtable is a modern spreadsheet tool with database functionalities. It&rsquo;s straightforward and user-friendly, allowing anyone to rapidly establish a database. It&rsquo;s one of the numerous no-code tools that&rsquo;s gaining popularity.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1639596019593/o_r5UmNVR.png" alt="screely-1639596010521.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="30-splitbeehttpssplitbeeio">30. <a href="https://splitbee.io/">Splitbee</a></h3>
<p>The analytics platform helps you to track and optimize your online business. Follow incoming traffic in real-time. Uncover where users come from and what pages they visit. Dive deep into your ad campaigns and see what converts best.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1639596155787/0vtELB9_4.png" alt="screely-1639596147000.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="31-voiceflowhttpswwwvoiceflowcom">31. <a href="https://www.voiceflow.com/">Voiceflow</a></h3>
<p>Voiceflow is a conversation design tool that allows teams to create, develop, and launch voice and chat assistants. Voiceflow makes it simple to create contextual discussions. Leverage reusable components, robust context models, interaction model exports, and more all inside our fast &amp; beautiful drag-n-drop canvas.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1639596362401/X3NMZhyZm.png" alt="screely-1639596349375.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="32-notionhttpswwwnotionso">32. <a href="https://www.notion.so/">Notion</a></h3>
<p>Notion is one of the most popular productivity apps right now, with over a million users. It continues to expand every day, owing to the adaptability of Notion&rsquo;s robust databases, user-friendly pages, and performance enhancements. You can also create webpages using notion.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1639596633959/rBgsARINh.png" alt="screely-1639596624427.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="33-taskadehttpswwwtaskadecom">33. <a href="https://www.taskade.com/">Taskade</a></h3>
<p>If you want Notion, Zoom, and Slack in one place then you definitely have to use this. Map out your workflow, from ideas to action. Collaborate on projects and manage tasks.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1639596957879/HHL4lQj0T.png" alt="screely-1639596949283.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="34-glidehttpswwwglideappscom">34. <a href="https://www.glideapps.com/">Glide</a></h3>
<p>Create powerful apps and websites, without code. Using basic spreadsheet skills, you can make incredible things with Glide. Pick a spreadsheet and Glide instantly generates a real, working app or website to get you started.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1639597085710/buKXhHAL8.png" alt="screely-1639597077629.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="35-bumpahttpsgetbumpacom">35. <a href="https://getbumpa.com/">Bumpa</a></h3>
<p>Manage your business from your phone. Everything you need to sell online, offline and on social media. Track orders. Engage customers. Receive payments. Free Website.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1639597274980/DKJEJe7Es.png" alt="screely-1639597262542.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="36-magicpatternhttpswwwmagicpatterndesign">36. <a href="https://www.magicpattern.design/">MagicPattern</a></h3>
<p>Beautiful graphics with a total of ten tools. Effortlessly and instantly! In just a few clicks, you can create distinctive visuals for social media posts, landing sites, and branding. Then you may save them as photos or even code (SVG &amp; CSS). Create an infinite number of high-quality backdrop graphics for your customers and products.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1639597442183/GEPrG3ZRp.png" alt="screely-1639597427099.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="37-shopifyhttpswwwshopifyin">37. <a href="https://www.shopify.in/">Shopify</a></h3>
<p>Shopify is an e-commerce platform that enables anybody to open an online store and sell their goods. With Shopify POS, merchants can also sell their items in person. Without any programming skills, you can set up a Shopify store and get it up and operating in no time. Themes are installed with a click of a button, and customising them (depending on the theme and its accessible parameters) is as simple as filling out an online form.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1639597686133/9duj-5vDd.png" alt="screely-1639597672214.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="38-graphitehttpsgraphitespace">38. <a href="https://graphite.space/">Graphite</a></h3>
<p>Responsive, Pixel-Perfect, Code-Free. Make site design feel like a comfortable environment. Create pixel-perfect Web Pages, not just mockups, with familiar visual editing tools. Concentrate on the creative aspect, and forget the rest.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1639597932532/3rbKuBYYH.png" alt="screely-1639597916091.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="39-testimonialhttpstestimonialto">39. <a href="https://testimonial.to/">Testimonial</a></h3>
<p>Easily get video testimonials from your customers. It is difficult it is to get video testimonials. As a result, Testimonial is there for you. You don&rsquo;t require a developer or website hosting to collect video testimonials from your consumers in minutes.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1639598165560/kPIX6Vgt_.png" alt="screely-1639598158194.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="40-carrdhttpscarrdco">40. <a href="https://carrd.co/">Carrd</a></h3>
<p>Carrd is a site-building platform similar to SquareSpace or WordPress that has grown in popularity over the last year. Carrd distinguishes itself from other websites by specializing in one-page websites. Almost all of its capabilities are free to use, and it has a wide range of applications.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1639598413517/HWzQBrWcp.png" alt="screely-1639598401311.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="41-ifttthttpsiftttcom">41. <a href="https://ifttt.com/">IFTTT</a></h3>
<p>IFTTT is short for If This Then That, and is the best way to integrate apps, devices, and services. IFTTT makes it possible for devices, services, and apps to interact in new and powerful ways. IFTTT was based on the idea that everything works better when it&rsquo;s done jointly. For anybody wanting to design a smart home or automate their life, tech incompatibility has become a challenge. It&rsquo;s simple with IFTTT.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1639598725228/ITwdxlHqu.png" alt="screely-1639598605485.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="42-nocode-videohttpswwwnocodevideo">42. <a href="https://www.nocode.video/">Nocode Video</a></h3>
<p>Explore top Nocode Videos from around the web and learn about new tech. Find tutorials related to Nocode.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1639599449648/YKACNFsNC.png" alt="screely-1639599439018.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="43-memberspacehttpswwwmemberspacecom">43. <a href="https://www.memberspace.com/">MemberSpace</a></h3>
<p>With just a few clicks, you can make any section of your website members-only. Simply restrict access to any page of your website, then decide how much visitors will pay to get access. Create memberships for whatever you desire, including courses, video lessons, member directories, and more, all while maintaining complete control over the design.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1639599622381/LbvuPe7wV.png" alt="screely-1639599568882.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="44-nocoderyhttpsdevnocoderycom">44. <a href="https://dev.nocodery.com/">NoCodery</a></h3>
<p>Nocodery is a job board for nocoders, created by nocoders for nocoders. Nocodery collects nocode job offers and jobs from a variety of sources so you don&rsquo;t have to search for them manually on job boards, saving you time!</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1639599877237/ExEReF5kA.png" alt="screely-1639599868920.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="45-codelesshowhttpscodelesshow">45. <a href="https://codeless.how/">Codeless.how</a></h3>
<p>Codeless is a website offering information for anyone who runs an internet business and wishes to automate routine operations without writing code. You&rsquo;ll learn how to use technologies like Zapier, Webflow, and Airtable to automate marketing, sales, billing, and other activities.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1639600090619/9iuWJNCpC.png" alt="screely-1639600075265.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="46softrhttpswwwsoftrio">46.<a href="https://www.softr.io/">Softr</a></h3>
<p>Softr is a fantastic online development tool that allows users to create code-free websites, portals, and web apps in only ten minutes on Airtable. Using Zapier, You may integrate application logic with external services or interconnect multiple sites.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1639600678403/8d-p2c3n4.png" alt="screely-1639600669490.png"  />
</p>
<p>People have been able to use computers without ever writing a line of code for decades. With the proliferation of no-code technologies, a comparable revolution is taking place for those who wish to write software. While the no-code revolution is still in its early stages, the business is expected to be worth more than $43 billion by 2023. The current boom, on the other hand, is the consequence of decades of hard labour and progress that cannot be overlooked.</p>
<h4 id="if-you--my-content-connect-me-on--twitterhttpsmobiletwittercomastrodevil_">If You ❤️ My Content! Connect Me on  <a href="https://mobile.twitter.com/Astrodevil_">Twitter</a></h4>



<a class="hugo-shortcodes-bmc-button" href="https://www.buymeacoffee.com/Astrodevil">
    <img src="https://img.buymeacoffee.com/button-api/?button_colour=ffdd00&amp;coffee_colour=ffffff&amp;emoji=&amp;font_colour=000000&amp;font_family=Cookie&amp;outline_colour=000000&amp;slug=Astrodevil&amp;text=Buy&#43;me&#43;a&#43;coffee" alt="Buy me a coffee" />
</a>

]]></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>