<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>websites on Mr. Ånand</title><link>https://mranand.com/tags/websites/</link><description>Recent content in websites on Mr. Ånand</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 10:56:05 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mranand.com/tags/websites/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Top 15 Must Try AI Tools for Professionals in 2023</title><link>https://mranand.com/blogs/top-15-must-try-ai-tools-for-professionals-in-2023/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 10:56:05 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://mranand.com/blogs/top-15-must-try-ai-tools-for-professionals-in-2023/</guid><description>In this article, we&amp;#39;ll see a few AI-powered tools that are set to revolutionize development and make the lives of professionals easy in 2023. We&amp;#39;ll talk about the top 15 AI and low-code tools designed to empower professionals. AI tools are so much more powerful now that they enable them to create impactful products, manage teams and run their own startups. Discover the cutting-edge capabilities of these AI tools and how they can significantly enhance efficiency and innovation in the development process.</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this article, we&rsquo;ll see a few AI-powered tools that are set to revolutionize development and make the lives of professionals easy in 2023. We&rsquo;ll talk about the top 15 AI and low-code tools designed to empower professionals. AI tools are so much more powerful now that they enable them to create impactful products, manage teams and run their own startups. Discover the cutting-edge capabilities of these AI tools and how they can significantly enhance efficiency and innovation in the development process.</p>
<h2 id="1picwishhttpspicwishcom">1. <a href="https://picwish.com/">PicWish</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://picwish.com/"><img loading="lazy" src="https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:700/1*wV7ukfKBpKSS1XjILO95jw.jpeg" alt=""  />
</a></p>
<p>PicWish is an all-in-one AI photo editor that can efficiently enhance<br>
your pictures within a few clicks. It has a <a href="https://picwish.com/remove-background">background remover</a> that can<br>
precisely cut-out the subject out of the picture and make the background<br>
transparent. Boosted by its AI technology, users can do this process<br>
automatically. For sure, people in the eCommerce business will love it<br>
as it can create professional product photos with ease. With this, it<br>
can even generate AI backgrounds after the background removal.</p>
<h2 id="2reccloudhttpsreccloudcomapptypechn-mr">2. <a href="https://reccloud.com/?apptype=chn-mr">RecCloud</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://reccloud.com/?apptype=chn-mr"><img loading="lazy" src="https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:700/1*ZlRh7WK7Mr4fdmS88iYmHg.png" alt=""  />
</a></p>
<p>This tool is designed to revolutionize the way content creators can integrate subtitles into videos, making the process effortlessly efficient and impressively accurate. Generate accurate subtitles with a simple click, saving you time and effort. Harness the power of cutting-edge AI for subtitles, with support for over 99 languages, your content becomes accessible to a global audience like never before. It also has tons of other AI tools and APIs support.</p>
<h2 id="3-bravohttpswwwbravostudioapp">3. <a href="https://www.bravostudio.app/">Bravo</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://www.bravostudio.app/"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1696095511382/d7d77b23-12f3-4084-9678-5947c39a26e1.png" alt=""  />
</a></p>
<p>Bravo Studio is a tool that connects the design and the backend to build a fully functional app. Unlike other app builders, Bravo leverages the design and data handling of third-party tools, adding flexibility to the process. You can use Figma or Adobe XD to design the UI and any backend with a REST API to store the data. By working directly with the app design, Bravo can ensure the app remains 100% true to design, whilst dramatically decreasing development time and providing sophisticated functionality. You can turn Figma designs into interactive prototypes with native features using Bravo Studio and showcase ideas in action, seamlessly publishing when ready</p>
<h2 id="4-fillouthttpswwwfilloutcomrefmra">4. <a href="https://www.fillout.com?ref=mra">Fillout</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://www.fillout.com?ref=mra"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1696096339534/df4b4eba-7446-4e60-a0c3-5c9b1e40971b.png" alt=""  />
</a></p>
<p>Fillout AI is a new tool that allows you to create forms, surveys, and quizzes in minutes. You can make a form from a doc, PDF, or text. The form builder is designed for HubSpot and allows you to collect or update data wherever you need it. You can connect your database or store responses in Fillout, drag and drop questions, and share a link or embed forms anywhere.</p>
<p>Fillout AI offers over 40 highly customizable question types and advanced features like accepting payments secured by Stripe, creating single or multi-page forms, and using beautifully crafted templates. It also provides templates for various types of forms such as RSVP forms, newsletter signups, price quote requests, employee emergency contact forms, and online registration forms.</p>
<h2 id="5-cronhttpscroncom">5. <a href="https://cron.com/">Cron</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://cron.com/"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1696096634488/878cb4d2-e6fb-4357-a6c1-e4c9bf1c4e3e.png" alt=""  />
</a></p>
<p>Cron Calendar is the next-generation calendar for professionals and teams. It’s a well-designed calendar app for Mac and Windows that features time zone features, meeting tools, and pleasantly-sounding notifications. Cron is a third-party calendar app that is also available for macOS, iOS, Windows, and the web. It’s an intuitive and well-thought-out app that has features you just don’t see from Google Calendar and other calendar apps. The main Cron window looks like a calendar app with a week view in the centre, a tiny month view in the corner and a list of active calendars on the left.</p>
<p>Cron Calendar is considered better by some users due to its unique features and beautiful design. It automatically syncs with Google Calendar and allows you to add events with one click, saving you the hassle of opening another window.</p>
<h2 id="6-tomehttpstomeapp">6. <a href="https://tome.app/">Tome</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://tome.app/"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1696097073024/8ceb1839-6b2f-4f31-ab17-ad6ba8cd5573.png" alt=""  />
</a></p>
<p>Tome is an AI-powered storytelling format that allows creators to quickly and easily construct complete stories, presentations, or outlines from scratch. It leverages the power of artificial intelligence to generate compelling presentations. By utilizing the capabilities of ChatGPT and DALL-E 2, it seamlessly combines text and images to create dynamic visual stories. You can type in a prompt and watch Tome generate entire narratives from scratch or create additional content pages within seconds. It comes with intelligent titles, pagination, page layouts, and page text, accompanied by GPT-3 and AI-generated graphics.</p>
<h2 id="7-superhumanhttpssuperhumancom">7. <a href="https://superhuman.com/">SuperHuman</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://superhuman.com/"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1696097607649/2768c6dc-b990-4c99-83dc-55f894e95ff9.png" alt=""  />
</a></p>
<p>Superhuman is an AI-powered email tool designed for high-performing teams and individuals, aiming to provide the fastest email experience ever made. It saves teams over 10 million hours every single year by allowing users to fly through their emails twice as fast as before. With Superhuman AI, you can write faster than ever before. Just jot down some phrases, and it will turn them into a full email.</p>
<p>The AI matches the voice and tone in the emails you’ve already sent, applying that to everything it creates. This results in an increase in productivity and a decrease in writer’s block. Superhuman also uses AI to automatically sort incoming messages based on your behavioral patterns, providing options for scheduling and setting reminders for important emails. It’s like having a professional editor just for you.</p>
<h2 id="8-tallyhttpstallysorefmr">8. <a href="https://tally.so?ref=mr">Tally</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://tally.so?ref=mr"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1696097985274/e615db22-3c34-4aac-85f9-d4da190cae20.png" alt=""  />
</a></p>
<p>Tally is a free online form builder that works like a text document. It’s the simplest way to create forms and is used by over 120,000+ teams at the world’s best companies. With Tally, you can just start typing on the page and insert blocks, similar to how you would in Notion. It provides unlimited forms, submissions, and everything you need to create professional forms and surveys — all free of charge as long as you stay within their fair usage guidelines.</p>
<h2 id="9-blackbox-aihttpswwwuseblackboxio">9. <a href="https://www.useblackbox.io/">Blackbox AI</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://www.useblackbox.io/"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1696098660853/af21a178-f1c4-46aa-92f8-39295133a490.png" alt=""  />
</a></p>
<p>Blackbox AI is an AI-powered coding assistant that helps developers code faster and better. It provides real-time code completion, documentation, and debugging suggestions. You can write any command starting with a double slash and hit enter to show suggestions. When it shows any suggestions, just hit the tab to accept and Esc to reject. It’s available in 20+ programming languages including Python, JavaScript, TypeScript, Go, Ruby, and much more. Blackbox AI also has a feature called Code Chat that allows developers to find the best code snippets to use while building products. The AI understands these queries and translates them into executable code. It can also identify potential errors in the user’s code and provide suggestions to correct them.</p>
<h2 id="10-loopinhttpswwwloopinhqcom">10. <a href="https://www.loopinhq.com/">Loopin</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://www.loopinhq.com/"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1696099003364/9a0dc80c-0cfe-4fe3-b08d-8e62f6762072.png" alt=""  />
</a></p>
<p>Loopin HQ is an AI Meeting Assistant designed specifically for customer-facing teams. It aims to revolutionize the way meetings are conducted by removing the hassle and providing concise meeting summaries, automated recaps, and a conversational assistant. Loopin uses state-of-the-art AI technology to transcribe meeting recordings and generate meeting minutes. You can focus on the conversation and never worry about making notes.</p>
<p>Loopin AI technology connects related meetings together to resurface important meetings and related notes. You can switch context within seconds and prepare for upcoming meetings with ease. If you want to know something, you can just ask Loopin AI. You can share meeting notes with your team via email, Slack, or Notion automatically.</p>
<h2 id="11-codiumhttpswwwcodiumai">11. <a href="https://www.codium.ai/">Codium</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://www.codium.ai/"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1696099273581/75f6585d-3029-440d-aff9-13926b0221ac.png" alt=""  />
</a></p>
<p>Codium AI is an AI-powered platform that helps development teams automate code reviews and identify potential issues in their code. It also writes test cases for the code that AI understands. Codium AI plugs into your IDE and suggests meaningful test suites as you code. It does this by exploring and analyzing your code, docstrings, and comments, and dynamically interacting with you. With CodiumAI, you get non-trivial tests (and trivial, too!) suggested right inside your IDE, so you can code smart, create more value, and stay confident when you push.</p>
<p>You get full visibility of how your code behaves and how the changes you make affect the rest of your code. You can spend fewer hours writing questionable test cases and more time developing useful features for your users. Unlike code coverage quotas, meaningful tests actually check your code’s functionality. So you get the confidence needed to commit.</p>
<h2 id="12-folkhttpswwwfolkapp">12. <a href="https://www.folk.app/">folk</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://www.folk.app/"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1696099555251/3f171362-2e01-40f1-96bf-c1388c53ac43.png" alt=""  />
</a></p>
<p>Folk CRM is an all-in-one CRM tool that helps you manage all your relationships, whether they’re related to sales, recruiting, fundraising, partnerships, or investing. It’s a collaborative workspace for your team’s relationships, and its AI-powered engine helps to personalize every touchpoint, write better, and track and monitor your results.</p>
<p>Folk allows you to sync contacts and interactions from anywhere, collaborate on pipelines with ease, generate emails with AI, personalize them at scale, track and follow up. It also offers analytics &amp; reports to help you make data-backed decisions. Folk is lightweight, customizable, and designed to work for you. It’s trusted by next-gen companies and offers a free plan up to 100 contacts in your personal CRM.</p>
<h2 id="13-writesonichttpswritesoniccom">13. <a href="https://writesonic.com/">Writesonic</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://writesonic.com/"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1696100153076/5a35466b-ab57-4ef2-a240-cd6aea1b59d2.png" alt=""  />
</a></p>
<p>Writesonic is an AI-powered content creation and customer experience platform that offers a variety of tools for different needs. It’s built on generative AI models and can create new content by learning from massive datasets. Writesonic’s online writer allows you to expand keywords into different styles of text in just a few minutes. It also comes with text editing, SEO optimization, landing page optimization, and other enhancements.</p>
<p>Writesonic provides a wide range of templates suitable for almost any content creation scenario. It also offers a feature called Chatsonic, which is a generative AI conversation partner powered by GPT-4 and designed to tackle ChatGPT’s limits. With Chatsonic’s Google Search integration, you can engage in real-time conversations on current events and trending topics effortlessly. Additionally, Writesonic offers Botsonic, a no-code AI chatbot builder that allows you to train ChatGPT on your own data and build smarter AI chatbots for your website.</p>
<h2 id="14-flair-aihttpsflairai">14. <a href="https://flair.ai/">Flair AI</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://flair.ai/"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1696100706341/8336c275-4a28-4089-99f5-92d6c20c2088.png" alt=""  />
</a></p>
<p>Flair AI is an AI-powered design tool specifically for product photography. It allows you to create stunning photoshoots in seconds by simply dragging and dropping images, props, and 3D assets. You can adjust the lighting and camera angle to compose the perfect scene. Flair AI also offers a new feature for fashion photoshoots where you can fit your cloth onto AI-generated models, creating high-quality on-model imagery at scale. It provides all the familiar tools you need to iterate on designs fast and build and share designs together with real-time collaboration. Moreover, you can leverage their API to create unique designs for your customers. It’s a highly useful tool when generating logos, product representations, and branded content in general.</p>
<h2 id="15-sudowritehttpswwwsudowritecom">15. <a href="https://www.sudowrite.com/">Sudowrite</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://www.sudowrite.com/"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1696100510644/eda6721d-6da1-43f4-b5c8-9702ad16915a.png" alt=""  />
</a></p>
<p>Sudowrite is an AI-powered creative writing tool that helps you write your novel or screenplay faster and more efficiently. It provides various “story tools” such as character development, world-building, and plot creation. Sudowrite is designed to help users overcome writer’s block, generate ideas, and enhance their writing. It can be deployed to generate new content, expand on existing content, or rewrite content to meet set criteria. The software can be used by novelists, screenwriters, and others with creative writing needs. Sudowrite is based on GPT-3 and GPT-4, 175+ billion parameter Transformer models, which learn general concepts from their training data. The model generates text by guessing what’s most likely to come next, one word at a time.</p>
<h2 id="16-vondyhttpsvondycomviamr">16. <a href="https://vondy.com/?via=mr">Vondy</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://www.vondy.com/?via=mr"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1696101026604/14ac2016-bad9-48db-b7b7-7ac278070412.png" alt=""  />
</a></p>
<p>Vondy AI is a next-generation AI platform that provides a variety of AI-powered apps to help enhance your productivity. It offers an extensive library of apps, characters, and prompts to help you create and explore. You can use Vondy to create your own apps, explore image generation tools, meet a collection of chatbots with unique personalities, and even find conversation starters. Vondy also offers a range of productivity apps, writing tools, and essential AI apps to get you started. It’s designed for teams of all sizes and technical backgrounds, allowing you to do more with less by creating, using, and sharing AI-powered tools tailored to your specific work needs.</p>
<h2 id="17-webwavehttpswebwavemeai-website-builder">17. <a href="https://webwave.me/ai-website-builder">WebWave</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://webwave.me/ref/12566526982"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1696095599682/73043c9c-d14e-4c39-a6f9-7856ba8ee46b.png" alt=""  />
</a></p>
<p>WebWave AI Website Builder is an innovative tool that allows you to generate a website with just one click. With a single click on the “Generate” button, the advanced algorithm creates a website tailored to your description. The AI generates the layout, images, colour palette, and fonts that best suit your description. However, you can tweak everything later with the drag-and-drop editor. The WebWave AI writer fills your page with copy that reflects your brand’s character. The SEO optimization feature ensures that your copy not only appeals to visitors but also to algorithms, leading to more traffic and clients. This platform is designed to be user-friendly and flexible, allowing you to create a website without needing any coding skills.</p>
<p><strong>I hope these tools and websites will help you in your professional work.</strong></p>
<h4 id="if-you--my-content-connect-me-on--twitterhttpsmobiletwittercomastrodevil_">If You ❤️ My Content! Connect Me on  <a href="https://mobile.twitter.com/Astrodevil_">Twitter</a></h4>



<a class="hugo-shortcodes-bmc-button" href="https://www.buymeacoffee.com/Astrodevil">
    <img src="https://img.buymeacoffee.com/button-api/?button_colour=ffdd00&amp;coffee_colour=ffffff&amp;emoji=&amp;font_colour=000000&amp;font_family=Cookie&amp;outline_colour=000000&amp;slug=Astrodevil&amp;text=Buy&#43;me&#43;a&#43;coffee" alt="Buy me a coffee" />
</a>

]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Top 20 Must Try AI Tools for Developers in 2023</title><link>https://mranand.com/blogs/top-20-must-try-ai-tools-for-developers-in-2023/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 10:56:05 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://mranand.com/blogs/top-20-must-try-ai-tools-for-developers-in-2023/</guid><description>In this article, We&amp;#39;ll talk about the top 20 AI and low-code tools designed to empower developers. AI tools are so much more powerful now that it enables them to create impactful products, manage teams and run their own startups. Discover the cutting-edge capabilities of these AI tools and how they can significantly enhance efficiency and innovation in the development process.</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this article, we&rsquo;ll see a few AI-powered tools that are set to revolutionize development and make the life of developers easy in 2023. We&rsquo;ll talk about the top 20 AI and low-code tools designed to empower developers. AI tools are so much more powerful now that it enables them to create impactful products, manage teams and run their own startups. Discover the cutting-edge capabilities of these AI tools and how they can significantly enhance efficiency and innovation in the development process.</p>
<h2 id="1-tldvhttpstldvcellosoaxf1wsxl27m">1. <a href="https://tldv.cello.so/AXf1WSXl27m">tl;dv</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://tldv.cello.so/AXf1WSXl27m"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1689492544546/f0dfc23d-b39a-44e4-b6c1-515488602cea.png" alt="tl;dv"  />
</a></p>
<p>Introducing <strong>tl;dv</strong>, an AI-powered tool for call and meeting management. With AI timestamps, you can effortlessly highlight key moments and automatically generate summaries. Get instant access to recordings, timestamps, and transcripts right after your calls. Quickly find important moments, create clips, and utilize AI search for comprehensive insights across your meeting library.</p>
<p>Whether it&rsquo;s UX research, product management, or customer success, This tool empowers you to enhance productivity, drive user-centric change, and streamline collaboration. Experience the transformative power of AI in optimizing your call workflows today.</p>
<h2 id="2-pieces-for-developershttpspiecesapp">2. <a href="https://pieces.app/">Pieces for Developers</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://pieces.app/"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1689632069086/84a29d20-d1df-4af4-bc1e-5075382bb334.png" alt="Pieces"  />
</a></p>
<p>Pieces for Developers is an intelligent code snippet manager deeply integrated with AI to help you save, generate, enrich, reuse and share code throughout your workflow. The desktop application and suite of integrations with existing developer tools boost your productivity while researching in the browser, collaborating with teammates, and coding in the IDE.</p>
<p>You can generate contextualized code based on your personal repository, extract code from screenshots, automatically add inline comments to your code, and much more - all within a powerful, centralized application that streamlines your workflow. Code more efficiently with their free tools!</p>
<h2 id="3-youhttpsyoucom">3. <a href="https://you.com/">YOU</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://you.com/"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1689493808498/b8a82560-f03d-4266-8720-f5d0ccfca39f.png" alt="YOU"  />
</a></p>
<p>You.com is a search engine built on artificial intelligence that provides users with a customized search experience while keeping their data 100% private. It&rsquo;s a proper app suite with lots of AI-based tools and features. With <strong>YOUwrite</strong>, you can use AI to write blogs, emails or social media posts. With <strong>YOUimagine,</strong> find and create stunning images using AI.</p>
<p>You can write code and take help in your development process by accessing code mode AI chat to search the web. And study or learn new skills by using study mode chat to access resources across the web. Explore YOU now.</p>
<h2 id="4-jamhttpsjamdev">4. <a href="https://jam.dev/">Jam</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://jam.dev/jamgpt"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1689580788138/6f5f6e55-73ca-41d4-b868-4209469ecaa8.png" alt="Jam"  />
</a></p>
<p>Jam.dev is a user-friendly tool trusted by thousands of teams. It enables quick bug reporting without disrupting workflow, generating comprehensive bug reports that include essential information like browser/OS details, console logs, user actions, network logs, and linked services. It seamlessly integrates with popular issue trackers and tools, enhancing bug reporting in any preferred platform.</p>
<p>Additionally, JamGPT, an AI debugging assistant included with Jam, analyzes bug reports, identifies correlations, and provides solutions, allowing for faster debugging powered by AI. JamGPT is available as a free extension for Jam users and as an instant ChatGPT app exclusively for macOS, accessible via a convenient keyboard shortcut.</p>
<h2 id="5-decktopus-aihttpswwwdecktopuscomviamr">5. <a href="https://www.decktopus.com/?via=mr">Decktopus AI</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://www.decktopus.com/?via=mr"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1689667688946/f8bbb738-5665-48f9-a2a3-3e8a04ea8097.png" alt="Decktopus"  />
</a></p>
<p>Decktopus is an invaluable tool for developers and product managers, enabling them to create impressive presentations effortlessly and without design expertise. By saving time and effort, it allows them to concentrate on essential tasks. For developers, Decktopus generates visually appealing presentations for project updates, technical documentation, and product demos, effectively conveying information to diverse audiences.</p>
<p>Product managers can utilize its features to craft engaging presentations for product roadmaps, market research, and customer feedback, utilizing customizable themes, layouts, and design options. Decktopus offers built-in tools such as forms, voice recording, custom domain integration, webhook functionality, and multimedia embedding, enhancing the overall presentation experience.</p>
<h2 id="6-durablehttpsdurableco">6. <a href="https://durable.co/">Durable</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://durable.co/"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1689876016105/a69c77ac-d9cf-46fa-8634-1b9a2a7fa377.png" alt=""  />
</a></p>
<p>Durable can help you build a website in 30 seconds with AI. This AI website builder generates an entire website with images and copies in seconds. If you are a small business owner without coding knowledge, this is a go-to tool for you. You can edit the website with a simple editor or generate a new website design just by writing AI prompts. You can get a website, CRM, analytics and add invoicing without any hectic process.</p>
<p>If you are a developer, you can launch a project page in seconds using Durable. Code less build more!</p>
<h2 id="7-leap-aihttpstryleapairefastro">7. <a href="https://tryleap.ai/?ref=astro">Leap AI</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://tryleap.ai/?ref=astro"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1689494296260/39dc28bd-2325-4e2e-8f2a-c9088f46be15.png" alt="Leap AI"  />
</a></p>
<p>Leap AI provides AI APIs for developers. Covers a wide range of AI tasks, including image recognition, text analysis, and natural language processing. Leap AI&rsquo;s APIs offer user-friendly features, making them accessible even for developers without AI experience. These APIs are scalable, allowing you to adjust the number of requests as per your needs. With reliable performance, you can trust that Leap AI&rsquo;s APIs will be available when required.</p>
<p>If you seek a provider with diverse services, easy-to-use APIs, and scalability, Leap AI is an excellent choice. Integrate with over 5,000+ apps without writing any code.</p>
<h2 id="8-notion-aihttpswwwnotionsoproductai">8. <a href="https://www.notion.so/product/ai">Notion AI</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://www.notion.so/product/ai"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1689497217522/91ff9f27-fb1a-48e0-a949-23ff97116449.png" alt="Notion"  />
</a></p>
<p>Notion AI is a helpful tool inside the Notion workspace, assisting with writing, brainstorming, editing, and summarizing. It boosts writing efficiency and speed, suitable for various content types like blogs, job descriptions, and emails. The &lsquo;Notion AI automates content creation, including blogs, brainstorming, to-do lists, and literature, using powerful artificial intelligence. Unlike other tools, Notion&rsquo;s drag-and-drop text editor allows easy rearrangement and transformation of AI-generated content.</p>
<h2 id="9-microsoft-designerhttpsdesignermicrosoftcom">9. <a href="https://designer.microsoft.com/">Microsoft Designer</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://designer.microsoft.com/"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1689497731903/5b68ec42-776c-4f51-ab56-bacda597d575.png" alt="MS"  />
</a></p>
<p>Microsoft Designer is a versatile tool for crafting signs, invitations, logos, social media posts, and website banners. With its AI capabilities, you can effortlessly begin designing using your own images or AI-generated options. It supports you throughout the creative journey, from ideation to actualization. Equipped with AI superpowers, it can generate striking designs and images based on your input, while providing writing assistance and automatic layout suggestions.</p>
<p>It can help you in the promotion of your software and apps by using visual design generated using AI.</p>
<h2 id="10-microsoft-clipchamphttpsclipchampcomen">10. <a href="https://clipchamp.com/en/">Microsoft Clipchamp</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://clipchamp.com/en/"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1689499024984/983ef9ca-0890-40b8-95c5-213a4b6b246a.png" alt="MS"  />
</a></p>
<p>Clipchamp is an online video editor that enables everyone to craft captivating stories through video. Clipchamp is the go-to platform for effortlessly editing videos for various purposes. Whether starting from scratch or using a template for efficiency, its extensive collection caters to all project types. Importing videos from multiple sources, including computers and mobile phones, is a breeze.</p>
<p>Microsoft is using AI like crazy, this video editor is super easy to use to edit presentations, video tutorials or project introductions. Automatically create accurate captions in over 140 languages. Turn text into speech with one click.</p>
<h2 id="11-superagihttpssuperagicom">11. <a href="https://superagi.com/">SuperAGI</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://superagi.com/"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1689533754815/091e8836-798a-4608-a49b-45c6ddc964cd.png" alt="SuperAGI"  />
</a></p>
<p>SuperAGI is a user-friendly open-source platform for building and launching autonomous agents for different purposes. With its graphical interface, action console, concurrent agents, and various database options, developers can easily create and manage AI agents. SuperAGI is a developer-focused framework for autonomous AI agents, designed to simplify the development process.</p>
<p>It recently introduced SuperCoder, a SuperAGI agent template to create simple software applications using goals &amp; instructions.</p>
<h2 id="12-replicatehttpsreplicatecom">12. <a href="https://replicate.com/">replicate</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://replicate.com/"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1689583036583/666a137e-da14-4dcf-b382-b9262cf4ac3b.png" alt="replicate"  />
</a></p>
<p>Replicate is a cloud-based platform that simplifies machine learning for developers. It offers a scalable API to run open-source models without requiring extensive knowledge of machine learning. Developers can access Replicate&rsquo;s Python library or directly query the API using their preferred tools. The platform hosts a diverse community of machine learning experts who share various models, from language processing to video creation.</p>
<p>With Replicate and tools like Next.js and Vercel, developers can swiftly bring their ideas to life and gain visibility on platforms like Hacker News. Replicate also streamlines model deployment with Cog, an open-source tool that packages models into production-ready containers. Overall, Replicate enables easy and efficient integration of machine learning into projects.</p>
<h2 id="13-hugging-facehttpshuggingfaceco">13. <a href="https://huggingface.co/">Hugging Face</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://huggingface.co/"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1689583354484/1ca9b760-f1b0-4a2c-9e57-a0e3471f24f1.png" alt="Hugging face"  />
</a></p>
<p>Hugging Face is an AI community shaping the future, enabling you to build, train, and deploy cutting-edge models using open-source machine learning. With over 5,000 organizations involved, Hugging Face provides a collaborative hub where creators tackle challenges in Audio, Vision, and Language with AI. Their natural language processing library, Transformers, is open-source and now supports various ML models like Flair, Asteroid, ESPnet, and Pyannote, with more on the way.</p>
<p>Additionally, Hugging Face offers an Inference API for seamless model deployment and the development of innovative technologies, including T0 Multitask Prompted Training, DistilBERT, HMTL, and Dynamical Language Models for enhanced language modeling.</p>
<h2 id="14-pineconehttpswwwpineconeio">14. <a href="https://www.pinecone.io/">Pinecone</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://www.pinecone.io/"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1689583592272/6084bde6-75f8-4e46-8340-540bf9bfd943.png" alt="Pinecone"  />
</a></p>
<p>Pinecone simplifies the development of high-performance vector search apps, offering scalability and ease of use. It empowers AI application builders with reduced overhead and ultra-low latencies, enabling a seamless transition from research to production without DevOps. With Pinecone, you can effortlessly launch, utilize, and scale your AI solution without the need for infrastructure maintenance or algorithm troubleshooting.</p>
<h2 id="15-midjourneyhttpswwwmidjourneycomhome">15. <a href="https://www.midjourney.com/home/">Midjourney</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://www.midjourney.com/home/"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1689588456524/c1614b7b-046d-45df-b944-7bcfcf4a48d7.png" alt="Midjourney"  />
</a></p>
<p>Midjourney is an AI-powered program that generates stunning images using advanced algorithms and state-of-the-art technology. It serves as a valuable tool for developers, enabling them to create visually appealing images for various projects, such as websites, apps, and games. Moreover, developers can leverage Midjourney to explore AI and machine learning techniques, integrating them into their own projects. By incorporating Midjourney, developers can enhance the visual appeal of their work and experiment with cutting-edge AI techniques, making it a powerful tool for their creative endeavours.</p>
<h2 id="16-assemblyaihttpswwwassemblyaicom">16. <a href="https://www.assemblyai.com/">AssemblyAI</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://www.assemblyai.com/"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1689588866426/5023d938-d984-49b1-8980-4f690cabf57c.png" alt="AssemblyAI"  />
</a></p>
<p>AssemblyAI is a leading platform that offers AI models for speech transcription and comprehension. Their user-friendly API provides access to advanced AI models that can recognize speakers, summarize speeches, and more. Leveraging cutting-edge AI research, AssemblyAI delivers reliable and scalable models through a secure API, trusted by numerous startups and enterprises worldwide. With comprehensive resources, including tutorials and documentation, developers can easily integrate AssemblyAI&rsquo;s API to create innovative products incorporating speech recognition and understanding. By utilizing AssemblyAI&rsquo;s state-of-the-art AI models, developers gain a powerful tool for accurately transcribing and comprehending speech data in their projects.</p>
<h2 id="17-chatpdfhttpswwwchatpdfcom">17. <a href="https://www.chatpdf.com/">ChatPDF</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://www.chatpdf.com/"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1689590014693/c7fdda50-7c9f-45f7-9b4c-1d2bb88decb6.png" alt="ChatPDF"  />
</a></p>
<p>ChatPDF is an AI platform that extracts information from PDFs, enabling users to chat with PDF files as if they were talking to a human. It is similar to ChatGPT, but specifically designed for research papers. To use ChatPDF, visit their website and upload a pdf. It offers a chat interface exclusively for interacting with PDFs in real time. This tool allows users to efficiently complete tasks and extract information from large PDF files. It accepts PDFs in any language and can chat in any language.</p>
<h2 id="18-agentgpthttpsagentgptreworkdai">18. <a href="https://agentgpt.reworkd.ai/">AgentGPT</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://agentgpt.reworkd.ai/"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1689591123085/4df55277-7362-4e3c-8663-9dbc87f6228c.png" alt="AgentGPT"  />
</a></p>
<p>AgentGPT is a platform that enables users to create and deploy their own autonomous AI agents online. Users can give their agents a name and objective, and the agents will work towards achieving the assigned goal. Through a chain of language models, the agents think, execute tasks, evaluate their performance, and generate new tasks, recursively advancing towards their objective. With AgentGPT, developers have a powerful tool for creating personalized AI agents capable of accomplishing diverse goals.</p>
<h2 id="19-langchainhttpslangchain-langchainvercelappdocsget_startedintroductionhtml">19. <a href="https://langchain-langchain.vercel.app/docs/get_started/introduction.html">LangChain</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://langchain-langchain.vercel.app/docs/get_started/introduction.html"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1689591738668/77b030c1-8d63-4d87-9dd5-1c3a28d4ccc0.png" alt="LangChain"  />
</a></p>
<p>LangChain is a framework that simplifies application development using large language models. It offers modular abstractions and implementations for various components, making it easy to work with language models. Additionally, LangChain provides customizable use-case-specific chains, enabling developers to quickly start and customize applications for specific purposes like document analysis, chatbots, and code analysis. Overall, LangChain empowers developers to leverage language models effectively and build innovative applications.</p>
<h2 id="20-gretelaihttpsgretelai">20. <a href="https://gretel.ai">Gretel.ai</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://gretel.ai"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1689592373298/9306e54d-cc0e-406f-a3b5-8a1877c1568c.png" alt="Gretel"  />
</a></p>
<p>Gretel ai is a synthetic data platform that enables developers to create artificial datasets resembling real data, ensuring privacy is maintained. With Gretel.ai&rsquo;s APIs, developers can easily generate anonymized and secure synthetic data, accelerating innovation while protecting sensitive information. The platform offers comprehensive tools for training AI models, validating use cases, and generating data as required, with a quick setup time. Developers can explore synthetic data through sample notebooks or the user-friendly web app, catering to both technical and non-technical users. Gretel ai empowers developers to harness the potential of synthetic data while upholding privacy standards.</p>
<p><strong>Few more tools&hellip;</strong></p>
<h2 id="21-merlinhttpsappgetmerlininplansrefnjjmztya">21. <a href="https://app.getmerlin.in/plans?ref=njjmztya">Merlin</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://app.getmerlin.in/plans?ref=njjmztya"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1690189472516/0ad35f9e-08ee-4d50-9a06-5b2295955287.png" alt=""  />
</a></p>
<p>Merlin is a Chrome extension powered by ChatGPT API that enhances your productivity by providing applications of ChatGPT on any website on your browser. It provides you with features like free access to the GPT-4 model by OpenAI, Youtube Summary, Blog Summary, AI writer for Gmail, Twitter &amp; LinkedIn, Chat GPT response on Google search, AI Chatbot to Chat with Merlin on any website and much more. It helps you get the best out of AI on Google Search, Youtube, Gmail, LinkedIn, Substack and 10+ million other websites.</p>
<h2 id="22-codewphttpscodewpai">22. <a href="https://codewp.ai/">CodeWP</a></h2>
<p><a href="https://codewp.ai/"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1689835584488/e1763aef-d00a-49d9-8b98-55134c81e37d.png" alt="CodeWP"  />
</a></p>
<p>CodeWP is a cutting-edge AI code generator and assistant built for WordPress. With its powerful features and user-friendly interface, it simplifies code creation, testing, and installation. It offers a vast library of verified snippets and tutorials to enhance your skills, making it a valuable tool for all aspects of WordPress development. Just ask the generator, and it will provide custom solutions tailored to your needs.</p>
<p><strong>I hope these AI-based tools and websites will help you as a developer to grow more.</strong></p>
<h4 id="if-you--my-content-connect-me-on--twitterhttpsmobiletwittercomastrodevil_">If You ❤️ My Content! Connect Me on  <a href="https://mobile.twitter.com/Astrodevil_">Twitter</a></h4>



<a class="hugo-shortcodes-bmc-button" href="https://www.buymeacoffee.com/Astrodevil">
    <img src="https://img.buymeacoffee.com/button-api/?button_colour=ffdd00&amp;coffee_colour=ffffff&amp;emoji=&amp;font_colour=000000&amp;font_family=Cookie&amp;outline_colour=000000&amp;slug=Astrodevil&amp;text=Buy&#43;me&#43;a&#43;coffee" alt="Buy me a coffee" />
</a>

]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>25 Must-Visit Killer Websites For Developers</title><link>https://mranand.com/blogs/25-must-visit-killer-websites-for-developers/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 17:31:05 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://mranand.com/blogs/25-must-visit-killer-websites-for-developers/</guid><description>There are so many websites to make the work of developers easier. Everyone doesn&amp;#39;t know all. In this article, we will see 25 Must-Visit Killer Websites For Developers. 90% of developers don’t know about these websites</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There are so many websites to make the work of developers easier. Everyone doesn&rsquo;t know all. In this article, we will see <strong>25 Must-Visit Killer Websites For Developers</strong>.</p>
<h3 id="1-devdocshttpsdevdocsio">1. <a href="https://devdocs.io/">DevDocs</a></h3>
<p>DevDocs brings together numerous API documentation in a single, searchable interface. You will find docs related to various programming languages, technologies in one place.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1638384967813/utLSXf2-U.png" alt="screely-1638384035935.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="2-raysohttpsrayso">2. <a href="https://ray.so/">ray.so</a></h3>
<p>This website allows you to take beautiful screenshots of codes. It also has a dark mode and some preloaded themes for different programming languages. You can also use its VS Code extension.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1638385311659/82S035d0k.png" alt="screely-1638385296060.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="3-poetsohttpspoetso">3. <a href="https://poet.so/">Poet.so</a></h3>
<p>This site is useful for developers who wish to post photos of their tweets on social media. Website transforms your tweet into a beautiful and editable design.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1638385530712/GsADMkksb.png" alt="screely-1638385516106.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="4-roadmapshhttpsroadmapsh">4. <a href="https://roadmap.sh/">roadmap.sh</a></h3>
<p>This website provides roadmaps, guidelines, and other educational content to assist developers in choosing a path and directing their learning. It is very helpful for a beginner as well as a learner who needs guidance.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1638385854363/V8bW_gzx1.png" alt="screely-1638385839901.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="5-lambdatesthttpswwwlambdatestcom">5. <a href="https://www.lambdatest.com/">LambdaTest</a></h3>
<p>LambdaTest is a cloud-based cross-browser testing platform that lets you test web applications on over 2000 different browsers, operating systems, and devices. LambdaTest allows you to test cross-browser compatibility both manually and automatically.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1638386119439/mDXT7rVtt.png" alt="screely-1638386105526.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="6-dailydevhttpsappdailydev">6. <a href="https://app.daily.dev/">daily.dev</a></h3>
<p>It is a platform where you can find so many good articles to read daily. It shows the best articles from various platforms directly in your feed. Stay updated with quality content from various platforms directly into your browser by using its extension.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1638386504039/glWhXS_nQ.png" alt="screely-1638386457871.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="7-showwcasehttpswwwshowwcasecom">7. <a href="https://www.showwcase.com/">Showwcase</a></h3>
<p>Showwcase is a new social media website specially for people who code connect, build community, and find new opportunities. It is a LinkedIn like platform but only focused on developers. You can join and <a href="https://www.showwcase.com/astrodevil">follow me</a> there.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1638386870736/KMtvp18LF.png" alt="screely-1638386858754.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="8-css-trickshttpscss-trickscom">8. <a href="https://css-tricks.com/">CSS-TRICKS</a></h3>
<p>You can master your web development skills by learning every basics about CSS from this website. If you didn&rsquo;t already know, CSS is what makes pages on the web look beautiful.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1638387360963/CZ40Lwai0.png" alt="screely-1638387302168.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="9-medusahttpswwwmedusajscom">9. <a href="https://www.medusajs.com/">Medusa</a></h3>
<p>An open-source Shopify alternative. Medusa is an open-source headless commerce engine that is fast and customizable. It&rsquo;s Free.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1638387765631/u99VAO5fh.png" alt="screely-1638387753072.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="10-smartmockupshttpssmartmockupscom">10. <a href="https://smartmockups.com/">SMARTMOCKUPS</a></h3>
<p>Why give your time learning how to use Photoshop. Smartmockups allow you to generate gorgeous high-resolution mockups straight in your browser and across numerous devices using a single interface. The quickest web-based mockup tool available, No prior experience or abilities are required, and the library of professional mockups is always growing.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1638388146151/XYY-Hey10.png" alt="screely-1638388121263.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="11-code-beautifyhttpscodebeautifyorg">11. <a href="https://codebeautify.org/">Code Beautify</a></h3>
<p>Make your source code more beautiful and easy to read using code to beautify its AI technology will make your source code more attractive and easy to read.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1638388669184/LkNccoLNs.png" alt="screely-1638388657726.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="12-overapihttpsoverapicom">12. <a href="https://overapi.com/">overAPI</a></h3>
<p>For all developers, OverAPI is one of the most beautiful and useful websites. This website has cheatsheets for the majority of programming languages. Take a look at it right now.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1638388599099/SWli6eqLd.png" alt="screely-1638388584887.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="13-responsivelyhttpsresponsivelyapp">13. <a href="https://responsively.app/">Responsively</a></h3>
<p>This is an open-source website that speeds up the development of web apps by 5 times. All target screens are displayed side by side in a single window. Reduces the time it takes to develop!</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1638388914941/fzDk1EbbW.png" alt="screely-1638388903814.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="14-color-hunthttpscolorhuntco">14. <a href="https://colorhunt.co/">Color Hunt</a></h3>
<p>Colorhunt is a website that allows you to select gorgeous colour palettes. Web designers will find it very beneficial to choose beautiful and appealing colours, as well as to accept colour recommendations from other artists and art projects.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1638389100098/2g69Ma1ju.png" alt="screely-1638389088000.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="15-carbonhttpscarbonnowsh">15. <a href="https://carbon.now.sh/">Carbon</a></h3>
<p>This website will help you to create and share beautiful images of your source codes. It also allows you to make changes to the photographs. You should give it a go right now.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1638389339711/JzN9a1yTi.png" alt="screely-1638389329198.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="16-meta-tagshttpsmetatagsio">16. <a href="https://metatags.io/">Meta Tags</a></h3>
<p>It is a website tag generator that also allows you to update and experiment with your content before seeing how it will appear on Google, Facebook, LinkedIn, and other social media sites.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1638389558917/vBV-rOHip.png" alt="screely-1638389538922.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="17-profile-pic-makerhttpspfpmakercom">17. <a href="https://pfpmaker.com/">Profile Pic Maker</a></h3>
<p>This website creates a professional and beautiful profile for each photo in your Web developer portfolio. As a developer, you will be exposed to social media. You only need to upload any of your images, and it will edit and enhance them. Give it a go right now.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1638389794694/Ywlpmxb0a.png" alt="screely-1638389786334.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="18-small-dev-toolshttpssmalldevtools">18. <a href="https://smalldev.tools/">Small Dev Tools</a></h3>
<p>This website offers a variety of free developer tools, including encoders/decoders, HTML/CSS/Javascript formatters, minifies, fake or test data generators, and more. It also allows you to share codes.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1638390009000/3vdcuU143.png" alt="screely-1638389956512.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="19-resumeiohttpsresumeio">19. <a href="https://resume.io/">resume.io</a></h3>
<p>This website allows you to create a quality resume. It will help you to create a professional resume by providing you with well-tested templates. Give it a Try.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1638390270548/U8e1MzxUy.png" alt="screely-1638390259749.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="20-codepenhttpscodepenio">20. <a href="https://codepen.io/">CODEPEN</a></h3>
<p>CodePen is a web-based development platform that allows users to modify front-end languages such as HTML, CSS, and JavaScript without having to install any software. The nicest aspect is that the findings are visible in real-time, making troubleshooting easier. Developers and designers can also exchange code samples (known as pens) with the rest of the world.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1638390510290/Z11dY_2Vv.png" alt="screely-1638390500404.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="21-storytalehttpsstorytaleio">21. <a href="https://storytale.io/">Storytale</a></h3>
<p>Storytale is a website that had collections of illustrations that Make your project eye-catching with awesome characters. It can be used personally and commercially. This is a helpful website for web designers. Get High-class assets for web and mobile projects.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1638390858191/-tZZB4fvS.png" alt="screely-1638390848756.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="22-readmesohttpsreadmeso">22. <a href="https://readme.so/">readme.so</a></h3>
<p>This website allows you to create project README very easily. Its simple editor helps you to quickly add and customize all the sections you need for your project&rsquo;s README. You can use this to create documentation of your open-source projects quickly.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1638391156722/7CiKyNZNv.png" alt="screely-1638391148567.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="23-peppertypehttpswwwpeppertypeai">23. <a href="https://www.peppertype.ai/">Peppertype</a></h3>
<p>Peppertype is a new tool that helps in automating the content production and ideation process. It analyses your business operations, understands your brand and target audience, and then creates fresh content for you using superior machine learning and artificial intelligence. If you are a developer creating content regularly, then this is for you.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1638391381010/rY_Fyi21N.png" alt="screely-1638391370901.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="24-synthesiahttpswwwsynthesiaio">24. <a href="https://www.synthesia.io/">synthesia</a></h3>
<p>Synthesia helps you to create AI-based videos in over 50+ languages. You don&rsquo;t need a camera, microphone, or real face to create video content. You just need to upload your script and you will get an AI video.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1638391829724/zFvA9ViJg.png" alt="screely-1638391816957.png"  />
</p>
<h3 id="25-programmer-humorhttpsprogrammerhumorio">25. <a href="https://programmerhumor.io/">Programmer Humor</a></h3>
<p>Even developers also need entertainment. You can visit this website for various memes and jokes related to programming and developers. Have Fun.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1638392080280/sDiDjjAgL.png" alt="screely-1638392067037.png"  />
</p>
<p><strong>Bonus Website</strong>: I used screenshots taken by <strong><a href="https://www.screely.com/">Screely</a></strong> in this Article.</p>
<h4 id="if-you--my-content-connect-me-on--twitterhttpsmobiletwittercomastrodevil_">If You ❤️ My Content! Connect Me on  <a href="https://mobile.twitter.com/Astrodevil_">Twitter</a></h4>



<a class="hugo-shortcodes-bmc-button" href="https://www.buymeacoffee.com/Astrodevil">
    <img src="https://img.buymeacoffee.com/button-api/?button_colour=ffdd00&amp;coffee_colour=ffffff&amp;emoji=&amp;font_colour=000000&amp;font_family=Cookie&amp;outline_colour=000000&amp;slug=Astrodevil&amp;text=Buy&#43;me&#43;a&#43;coffee" alt="Buy me a coffee" />
</a>

]]></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>