<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>career on Mr. Ånand</title><link>https://mranand.com/tags/career/</link><description>Recent content in career on Mr. Ånand</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 22:12:05 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mranand.com/tags/career/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>GirlScript Summer of Code Learning And Experiences: From Contributor To Project Admin</title><link>https://mranand.com/blogs/girlscript-summer-of-code-learning-and-experiences/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 22:12:05 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://mranand.com/blogs/girlscript-summer-of-code-learning-and-experiences/</guid><description>GSSoC stands for GirlScript Summer of Code. It is a three-month-long Open-Source Program conducted by the GirlScript Foundation for beginners. This year I am selected as project admin for the program. (GSSOC&amp;#39;22)
In this article, I am going to share my experiences from being a contributor in an open-source program to the project admin &amp;amp; mentor of one.</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>GSSoC stands for <a href="https://gssoc.girlscript.tech/">GirlScript Summer of Code</a>. It is a three-month-long Open-Source Program conducted by the GirlScript Foundation for beginners. This year I am selected as project admin for the program. (GSSOC'22)</p>
<p>In this article, I am going to share my experiences from being a contributor in an open-source program to the project admin &amp; mentor of one.</p>
<h3 id="how-i-started">How I started?</h3>
<p>My first open-source contribution was to a friend&rsquo;s repository. After doing some small contributions I came to know about GSSoC program and I took part in it. This was the first big contribution from my side to any open source project. Before that, I had some experience contributing to <strong>EbookFoundation / free-programming-books</strong>. From that, I learned to communicate over issues and to make pull requests properly. This previous work helped me a lot during GirlScript Summer of Code.</p>
<h3 id="what-i-learned">What I Learned?</h3>
<p>Successful contributions during the program definitely acted as a confidence booster for me. Now, I was more confident to work on any open-source project. While contributing I went through some issues and pull requests where project maintainers were discussing things and I tried to understand their workflow, and how they manage things.</p>
<p>After some time, I decided to take part as a project admin in an open-source program. Hacktoberfest was the best time to do so because many newbies were going to start their open source contributions in the month of October.</p>
<h3 id="what-next">What Next?</h3>
<p>I had created a repository to host small JavaScript projects. It was for personal use first but after the decision of participating as a project admin, I created a GitHub organization <a href="https://github.com/ZeroOctave">ZeroOctave</a> and added the same repository inside that. Hacktoberfest was going to start so I thought of taking my chances and as expected some good contributions were added to the repository. I was enjoying my role as a maintainer while guiding contributors for the contribution to my repository.</p>
<p>Just after Hacktoberfest, some more open-source programs were going to start so I applied with my repository and got accepted in two of them. Those programs were <a href="https://icc-techsahead.netlify.app/">Infinite Clone Conspiracy</a> &amp; <a href="https://dwoc.io/">DWoC'21</a>. These programs were not big enough to attract many contributors but still some good projects were added to our repository and some new members also joined the GitHub organization.</p>
<h3 id="gssoc">GSSoC!</h3>
<p>GSSoC stands for <s>Google</s> GirlScript Summer of Code. As I mentioned earlier, GSSoC'21 acted as the starting step for my open source journey. After 1 year when another version of GSSoC came back, I decided to participate in my project this time. I filled out the registration form with my organization and project details and got selected as project admin. It&rsquo;s a 3-month long program currently going on, many new contributions are coming into our organization repository. <a href="https://github.com/ZeroOctave/ZeroOctave-Javascript-Projects">ZeroOctave Javascript Projects</a> is our project repository that is the part of GSSoC'22. Till now 200+ issues created and 200+ pull requests merged.</p>
<p>While doing my work as project admin and coordinating with my project maintainers, I am also focused on enhancing my tech skills. So that I can contribute to some good open-source projects out there.</p>
<h3 id="invitation-for-you">Invitation For You!</h3>
<p>If you are a beginner, you are welcome to contribute to our organization. If you are an active open source contributor or maintainer, you are welcome to join ZeroOctave. Join zeroOctave to add your projects, guide newbies or write articles related to open source.</p>
<p><strong>Invitation Links</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://github.com/ZeroOctave"> Join ZeroOctave GitHub Organization</a></li>
<li><a href="https://github.com/ZeroOctave#what-you-can-do-here">Contribute In Projects</a></li>
<li><a href="https://hashnode.com/teams/invite/0013e746-aa30-4335-9196-5dd3bed50715">Join ZeroOctave Blog Team</a></li>
</ul>
<h4 id="if-you--my-content-connect-me-on--twitterhttpsmobiletwittercomastrodevil_-or-supports-me-by-buying-me-a-coffeehttpswwwbuymeacoffeecomastrodevil">If You ❤️ My Content! Connect Me on  <a href="https://mobile.twitter.com/Astrodevil_">Twitter</a> or Supports Me By <a href="https://www.buymeacoffee.com/Astrodevil">Buying Me A Coffee☕</a></h4>
]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Make Your GitHub Profile Standout To Attract Better Opportunities</title><link>https://mranand.com/blogs/make-your-github-profile-standout-to-attract-better-opportunities/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 11:00:05 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://mranand.com/blogs/make-your-github-profile-standout-to-attract-better-opportunities/</guid><description>To screen candidates, the industry is shifting away from resumes and toward GitHub profiles. In the software industry, Open Source projects are widely regarded now. How can recruiters know that the abilities you claim to have are truly the skills you have? When you&amp;#39;re a fresher with no professional experience open-source contributions come in useful. Without any prior industry expertise, GitHub allows you to exhibit your work. As a result, it&amp;#39;s important to make GitHub Profile stand out and present the best version of yourself.</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>To screen candidates, the industry is shifting away from resumes and toward GitHub profiles. In the software industry, Open Source projects are widely regarded now. How can recruiters know that the abilities you claim to have are truly the skills you have? When you&rsquo;re a fresher with no professional experience open-source contributions come in useful. Without any prior industry expertise, GitHub allows you to exhibit your work. As a result, it&rsquo;s important to make GitHub Profile stand out and present the best version of yourself.</p>
<p>In this article, I am shedding light on tips to <strong>Make Your GitHub Profile Standout To Attract Better Opportunities</strong>.</p>
<h2 id="introduction">Introduction!</h2>
<p><a href="https://github.com/Astrodevil"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1643986105138/0oFtVvL6rO.png" alt="screely-1643985124626.png"  />
</a></p>
<p>The above screenshot is of my GitHub profile. I have mentioned my bio in a detailed manner, including contribution graphs, badges, tech stack, proper name, username, profile picture, social handles, and my side hustles. You can also create your GitHub profile like mine or even better. Isn&rsquo;t my profile more detailed and attractive than resume? I hope after seeing the above screenshot you also want to make your GitHub profile stand out. <em>Let&rsquo;s get started!</em></p>
<h2 id="foundation-stone">Foundation Stone</h2>
<p>As you know already, the repository is the main feature of GitHub where every project, content, code is stored properly.</p>
<p>Let&rsquo;s start by creating a special repository after signing in to your GitHub account. <strong>This repository name must be same as your GitHub username</strong>.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1643985010957/IkhnHnKtE.png" alt="screely-1643984983985.png"  />
</p>
<p>This is a ✨special ✨ repository that you can use to add a <a href="https://docs.github.com/en/repositories/managing-your-repositorys-settings-and-features/customizing-your-repository/about-readmes">README.md</a> to your GitHub profile. Make sure it’s public and initialize it with a README or create a README.md file inside this repository to get started.</p>
<p><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Markdown">Markdown</a> will be used to add contents and details in <a href="https://docs.github.com/en/repositories/managing-your-repositorys-settings-and-features/customizing-your-repository/about-readmes">README</a> file. Learn Markdown syntax from this <a href="https://github.com/Astrodevil/Open-Source-Gallery/blob/main/src/markdown-cheatsheet.pdf">cheetsheet</a>. README files are commonly used to write documentation for the project repositories.</p>
<p>It&rsquo;s time to add contents in your profile README.</p>
<ul>
<li>
<h3 id="header">Header</h3>
</li>
</ul>
<p>In the header, you can add your name, greet message, photo or gif, or nothing according to your choice. I am using my profile-related codes, you can change accordingly.</p>
<pre tabindex="0"><code># Hi, I&#39;m Astrodevil &lt;img src=&#34;https://github.com/TheDudeThatCode/TheDudeThatCode/blob/master/Assets/Hi.gif&#34; width=&#34;29px&#34;&gt;
</code></pre><p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1643988124430/yV3R85kVl.png" alt="screely-1643988107672.png"  />
</p>
<ul>
<li>
<h3 id="about">About</h3>
</li>
</ul>
<p>In the About section you can add your little introduction, What you are working on, What are your goals or something like that.</p>
<pre tabindex="0"><code># replace contents according to you.
&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td valign=&#34;center&#34;&gt;
      🎓 I am currently pursuing my **Bachelor&#39;s in Computer Science Engineering**.
      🌱 I am currently learning **Java** and also interested in **Web Development**.
      🎯 My Goal is to Contribute to as many **open source project** as possible.
      ✨ I love to create different types of **contents**.
&lt;td &gt;
# this is my daily.dev card, you can edit this accordingly
      &lt;a href=&#34;https://app.daily.dev/Astrodevil&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://api.daily.dev/devcards/81fef2c2311f4739a063dbde61b40fe2.png?r=1fr&#34; width=&#34;300&#34; alt=&#34;Mr. Ånand&#39;s Dev Card&#34;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;/td&gt;
    
  &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/table&gt;
</code></pre><p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1643990740258/Z1jZcLM6f.png" alt="screely-1643989115241.png"  />
</p>
<ul>
<li>
<h3 id="contribution-graph">Contribution Graph</h3>
</li>
</ul>
<p>I have added a contribution graph banner to update daily activity from my GitHub profile. It&rsquo;s a nice way to showcase if you are active frequently and doing some contributions in projects. This graph is updating daily automatically.</p>
<pre tabindex="0"><code> # replace username with your own or change theme
![GitHub Activity Graph](https://activity-graph.herokuapp.com/graph?username=#your-username&amp;theme=dracula&amp;hide_border=true)
</code></pre><p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1643999148850/TYksn6HXu.png" alt="screely-1643999127515.png"  />
</p>
<ul>
<li>
<h3 id="icons--badges">Icons &amp; Badges</h3>
</li>
</ul>
<p>Adding <strong>social handles</strong> on GitHub profile is the best way to connect with peoples and transfer more audience towards your socials. You can use badges for that or icons. You can create badges from <a href="https://shields.io/">shields.io</a> and also use icons from <a href="https://www.flaticon.com/free-icons/social-media">flaticon</a>. There are tons of site to find attractive icons. You can also add information about your tech stack and tools you are familiar with by using badges and icons.
<img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1644000346031/NDAKl8FYz.png" alt="screely-1644000227962.png"  />

<a href="https://github.com/adityaoberai"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1644000356557/-3x4Rkzzb.png" alt="screely-1644000240039.png"  />
</a></p>
<ul>
<li>
<h3 id="stats-card">Stats Card</h3>
</li>
</ul>
<p>Adding Stats cards to your GitHub page is another common profile enhancement. This is a simple method to display all of your GitHub statistics in a fun, visual way. You can also track your GitHub Streak.</p>
<pre tabindex="0"><code># replace username with your own or change theme
## Stats📈
&lt;p align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;
&lt;img width=&#34;40%&#34; src=&#34;https://github-readme-stats.vercel.app/api/top-langs?username=#your-username&amp;show_icons=true&amp;theme=dracula&amp;title_color=ff8000&amp;text_color=ffffff&amp;bg_color=6a6a6a&amp;locale=en&amp;layout=compact&amp;hide_border=true&#34; alt=&#34;#your-username&#34; /&gt; 
&lt;img width=&#34;48%&#34; src=&#34;https://github-readme-stats.vercel.app/api?username=#your-username&amp;show_icons=true&amp;theme=dracula&amp;title_color=ff8000&amp;text_color=ffffff&amp;bg_color=6a6a6a&amp;locale=en&amp;hide_border=true&#34; alt=&#34;#your-username&#34; /&gt;
&lt;img width=&#34;48%&#34; src=&#34;https://github-readme-streak-stats.herokuapp.com/?user=#your-username&amp;theme=highcontrast&amp;hide_border=true&#34; alt=&#34;#your-username&#34; /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
</code></pre><p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1644001673972/Aa_oIfn4V.png" alt="screely-1644001425832.png"  />
</p>
<p>These are the basic customization method that can make your GitHub profile stand out, I used my profile as an example to explain above. You can also add more customization in your GitHub profile README to make it detailed and attractive. <em>Let&rsquo;s see that in next section</em>.</p>
<h2 id="building">Building</h2>
<ul>
<li>You can also <strong>track your activity</strong> and showcase it on your profile README by using a GitHub Action Scripts. Just create <code>/.github/workflows/update-readme.yml</code> inside the repository and paste below code inside update-readme.yml file. This script updates activity every 30 minutes.</li>
</ul>
<pre tabindex="0"><code>name: Update README

on:
  schedule:
    - cron: &#39;*/30 * * * *&#39;
  workflow_dispatch:

jobs:
  build:
    runs-on: ubuntu-latest
    name: Update this repo&#39;s README with recent activity

    steps:
      - uses: actions/checkout@v2
      - uses: jamesgeorge007/github-activity-readme@master
        env:
          GITHUB_TOKEN: ${{ secrets.GITHUB_TOKEN }}
</code></pre><p>Add this block to README.md file where you want to showcase your recent activity</p>
<pre tabindex="0"><code>
&lt;!--START_SECTION:activity--&gt;
&lt;!--END_SECTION:activity--&gt;
</code></pre><p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1644003241309/oKOBcwt09.png" alt="screely-1644003225209.png"  />
</p>
<ul>
<li>You can also add your <strong>blogs and side hustles</strong> on your profile README by manually adding it or automating the tasks by using GitHub Actions. Check this <a href="https://astrodevil.hashnode.dev/some-cool-github-actions-you-wont-believe-exists">article</a> to know more about helpful actions. You can impress recruiters by showcasing your awesome side hustles.</li>
</ul>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.hashnode.com/res/hashnode/image/upload/v1644005000197/gFSVDnWjN.png" alt="screely-1644004991863.png"  />
</p>
<h2 id="final-touch">Final Touch</h2>
<ul>
<li>
<p>If you don&rsquo;t want to learn Markdown or don&rsquo;t have enough time to write from scratch. You can use <a href="https://rahuldkjain.github.io/gh-profile-readme-generator/">GitHub Profile README Generator</a>, <a href="https://gprm.itsvg.in/">GPRM</a> or <a href="https://readme.so/">readme generator</a> to create your profile README.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>You can also take inspiration from other profiles by copy-pasting markdown codes in your README to customize accordingly. Here are the <a href="https://eddiehubcommunity.github.io/awesome-github-profiles/profiles">example profiles</a> you can take inspiration from.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p>I hope, This will help you to make your GitHub profile stand-out! What are you waiting for? Now go create your own profile README and open a world of opportunities for yourself. Check out my <a href="https://github.com/Astrodevil">GitHub</a>🤝</p>
<h4 id="if-you--my-content-connect-me-on--twitterhttpsmobiletwittercomastrodevil_-or-supports-me-by-buying-me-a-coffeehttpswwwbuymeacoffeecomastrodevil">If You ❤️ My Content! Connect Me on  <a href="https://mobile.twitter.com/Astrodevil_">Twitter</a> or Supports Me By <a href="https://www.buymeacoffee.com/Astrodevil">Buying Me A Coffee☕</a></h4>
]]></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>